<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>NEWS IN ENGLISH</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/rss</link><description>NEWS IN ENGLISH</description><copyright>NHL Enterprises, L.P. (c) 2015 NHL. All Rights Reserved</copyright><language>en_US</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2015 16:11:37 EDT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Pulkkinen scores twice, Red Wings dominate Malkin-less Penguins 5-1</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=758126</link><description>&#xD;
PITTSBURGH, Pa. - Teemu Pulkkinen scored twice for the first multigoal game of his career and the Detroit Red Wings thrashed the Pittsburgh Penguins 5-1 on Sunday.&#xD;
&#xD;
Marek Zidlicky added a goal and two assists for the Red Wings. Henrik Zetterbe...</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2015 15:25:01 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=758126</guid></item><item><title>Penguins star Sidney Crosby a game-time decision against Red Wings; Evgeni Malkin out</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=758124</link><description>&#xD;
PITTSBURGH, Pa. - Pittsburgh Penguins captain Sidney Crosby could return to the lineup on Sunday afternoon against Detroit.&#xD;
&#xD;
Crosby missed Saturday's 2-0 loss to Boston after falling ill following pregame warmups. Coach Mike Johnston said Sund...</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2015 11:55:01 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=758124</guid></item><item><title>Around the League notebook for Saturday, March 14</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=758193</link><description>SATURDAY'S RESULTS&#xD;
Home Team in Caps&#xD;
PHILADELPHIA 7, Detroit 2&#xD;
Boston 2, PITTSBURGH 0&#xD;
Chicago 6, SAN JOSE 2&#xD;
NY Rangers 2, BUFFALO 0&#xD;
Winnipeg 2, TAMPA BAY 1&#xD;
Montreal 3, NY ISLANDERS 1&#xD;
Florida 2, CAROLINA 0&#xD;
VANCOUVER 4, Toronto 1&#xD;
Minnesota...</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2015 11:07:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://1.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/2015/03/plekanec-cze-0314.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=758193</guid></item><item><title>Rogers Hometown Hockey: Regina, Saskatchewan</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757933</link><description>CITY in Canada will televise "Rogers Hometown Hockey" on Sunday at 6:30 p.m. ET, prior to the game between the Philadelphia Flyers and Ottawa Senators. The show will also air on NHL Network in the U.S. The location this week is Regina, Saskatchewa...</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2015 03:00:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://3.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/gallery/2015/02/464768_1423431969670.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757933</guid></item><item><title>WHL Roundup: Colby Cave scores four times as Broncos rout Raiders</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=758172</link><description>&#xD;
SWIFT CURRENT, Sask. - Colby Cave scored four times and added an assist as the Swift Current Broncos routed the Prince Albert Raiders 7-3 on Saturday night in Western Hockey League action.&#xD;
&#xD;
Jake DeBrusk had a four-point night — including two g...</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2015 02:24:02 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=758172</guid></item><item><title>Alex Tanguay, Semyon Varlamov help Avalanche hold off Flames 3-2</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=758122</link><description>&#xD;
DENVER - Alex Tanguay and Ryan O'Reilly scored 1:47 apart in the second period, Semyon Varlamov stopped 29 shots and the Colorado Avalanche held off the Calgary Flames 3-2 on Saturday night.&#xD;
&#xD;
John Mitchell added another goal for the Avalanche,...</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2015 00:55:00 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=758122</guid></item><item><title>Niederreiter, Brodziak score 17 seconds apart late in 3rd, Wild beat Blues 3-1</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=758120</link><description>&#xD;
ST. LOUIS - Devan Dubnyk found a pretty good way to forget his poor past against St. Louis.&#xD;
&#xD;
Win.&#xD;
&#xD;
Dubnyk made a season-high 41 saves and Nino Niederreiter and Kyle Brodziak scored just 17 seconds apart in the third period as the Minnesota W...</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2015 00:45:02 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=758120</guid></item><item><title>NHL Capsules</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=758119</link><description>&#xD;
PITTSBURGH, Pa. - Tuukka Rask made 30 saves and the Boston Bruins won their fifth straight, 2-0 over a Pittsburgh Penguins team missing Sidney Crosby and minus Evgeni Malkin for most of the game Saturday.&#xD;
&#xD;
Crosby, the Penguins' leading scorer,...</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2015 00:15:02 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=758119</guid></item><item><title>Cammalleri gets 25th, Devils score 3 in 3rd to beat Coyotes 4-1 and avoid winless trip</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=758118</link><description>&#xD;
GLENDALE, Ariz. - Mike Cammalleri scored his 25th goal in a three-goal third period, Cory Schneider stopped 30 shots and the New Jersey Devils beat the Arizona Coyotes 4-1 Saturday night to avoid a winless road trip.&#xD;
&#xD;
Jordin Tootoo had a goal ...</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2015 00:05:11 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=758118</guid></item><item><title>Montreal goalie Carey Price unwinds during tight NHL game by taking selfie with young fan</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=758117</link><description>&#xD;
UNIONDALE, N.Y. - How does Montreal goaltender Carey Price find time to relax during a game? By taking a selfie, of course.&#xD;
&#xD;
During a TV timeout late in the third period of a game against the New York Islanders, Price skated over to the boards...</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2015 23:55:01 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=758117</guid></item><item><title>Niederreiter, Brodziak score 17 seconds apart late in 3rd, Wild beat Blues 3-1</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=758116</link><description>&#xD;
ST. LOUIS - Nino Neiderreiter and Kyle Brodziak scored just 17 seconds apart late in the third period Saturday night, giving the Minnesota Wild a 3-1 win over the St. Louis Blues.&#xD;
&#xD;
Devan Dubnyk made 40 saves for the Wild (38-24-7), who had los...</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2015 23:05:01 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=758116</guid></item><item><title>OHL Roundup: Bennett scores hat trick as Frontenacs beat Battalion</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=758161</link><description>&#xD;
KINGSTON, Ont. - Calgary Flames prospect Sam Bennett continues to shine since returning to the Ontario Hockey League.&#xD;
&#xD;
Bennett had a hat trick and added an assist as the Kingston Frontenacs won their fifth straight by shutting out the North Ba...</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2015 23:04:01 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=758161</guid></item><item><title>South Carolina sets ECHL mark with 18th straight win</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=758104</link><description>The South Carolina Stingrays set an ECHL record with their 18th straight win, 6-0 against the Gwinnett Gladiators at the North Charleston Coliseum on Saturday.&#xD;
&#xD;
The record of 17 was set by the Cincinnati Cyclones from Jan. 13-Feb. 29, 2008.&#xD;
&#xD;
T...</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2015 22:22:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://2.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/2014/08/ECHL1.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=758104</guid></item><item><title>Stafford and Wheeler score 3rd period goals, Jets rally to beat Lightning 2-1</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=758115</link><description>&#xD;
TAMPA, Fla. - Drew Stafford and Blake Wheeler scored third-period goals as the Winnipeg Jets rallied to beat the Tampa Bay Lightning 2-1 on Saturday night.&#xD;
&#xD;
Ondrej Pavelec made 15 saves for the Jets, who are in the mix for a Western Conference...</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2015 22:15:04 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=758115</guid></item><item><title>Ellis stops 27 shots as Panthers shut out Hurricanes 2-0</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=758113</link><description>&#xD;
RALEIGH, N.C. - Dan Ellis made 27 saves for his first shutout of the season, and Brandon Pirri scored in the second period to lead the Florida Panthers to a 2-0 victory over the Carolina Hurricanes on Saturday night.&#xD;
&#xD;
Dave Bolland added an emp...</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2015 22:05:01 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=758113</guid></item><item><title>QMJHL Roundup: Garland scores twice, adds two assists as Wildcats double up Titan</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=758032</link><description>&#xD;
MONCTON, N.B. - Conor Garland scored twice and added two assists as the Moncton Wildcats doubled up the Acadie-Bathurst Titan 8-4 on Saturday in Quebec Major Junior Hockey League action.&#xD;
&#xD;
Taylor Burke had a pair of goals for Moncton (45-17-3) ...</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2015 22:04:01 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=758032</guid></item><item><title>Granlund with a pair of goals as Flames edge Marlies 5-4</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=758012</link><description>&#xD;
GLEN FALLS, N.Y. - Markus Granlund scored twice and Doug Carr made 35 saves as the Adirondack Flames edged the visiting Toronto Marlies 5-4 on Saturday in American Hockey League action.&#xD;
&#xD;
Devin Setoguchi added a goal and an assist for the Flame...</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2015 21:55:03 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=758012</guid></item><item><title>Skapski's first shutout, Yandle's third-period goal lift Rangers past Sabres 2-0</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=758010</link><description>&#xD;
BUFFALO, N.Y. - Keith Yandle's third-period goal helped lift the New York Rangers to a 2-0 win over the Buffalo Sabres on Saturday night.&#xD;
&#xD;
Martin St. Louis added an empty-net goal and Mackenzie Skapski made 20 saves for his first career NHL sh...</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2015 21:45:06 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=758010</guid></item><item><title>Forbort scores twice as Manchester Monarchs down St. John's IceCaps 4-1</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=758009</link><description>&#xD;
ST. JOHN'S, N.L. - Derek Forbort had a pair of goals as the Manchester Monarchs downed the host St. John's IceCaps 4-1 on Saturday in American Hockey League action.&#xD;
&#xD;
Vincent LoVerde and Sean Backman also scored for the Monarchs (38-15-8), who ...</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2015 21:35:01 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=758009</guid></item><item><title>Cherry bets Kadri will eventually leave Toronto after being humiliated</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=758008</link><description>&#xD;
TORONTO - Don Cherry says benching Nazem Kadri for three games could come back to haunt the Toronto Maple Leafs.&#xD;
&#xD;
Speaking on his weekly Coaches Corner segment on Hockey Night in Canada, Cherry was supportive of Kadri and says the way the 24-y...</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2015 20:55:00 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=758008</guid></item><item><title>NHL Capsules</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=758007</link><description>&#xD;
PITTSBURGH, Pa. - Tuukka Rask made 30 saves and the Boston Bruins won their fifth straight, 2-0 over a Pittsburgh Penguins team missing Sidney Crosby and minus Evgeni Malkin for most of the game Saturday.&#xD;
&#xD;
Crosby, the Penguins' leading scorer,...</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2015 19:55:01 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=758007</guid></item><item><title>Crosby late scratch for Penguins; Malkin injured</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=758052</link><description>PITTSBURGH -- The Pittsburgh Penguins started their game Saturday without Sidney Crosby and finished it without Evgeni Malkin.&#xD;
&#xD;
Crosby was a late scratch against the Boston Bruins at Consol Energy Center for unspecified reasons after participati...</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2015 17:00:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://1.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/2015/03/BRUINS_PENGUINS_031415.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=758052</guid></item><item><title>Philadelphia's Brayden Schenn scores 2 goals to lead Flyers to 7-2 rout of Red Wings</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=758005</link><description>&#xD;
PHILADELPHIA - Brayden Schenn scored a pair of goals to lead the Philadelphia Flyers to a 7-2 rout of the slumping Detroit Red Wings on Saturday.&#xD;
&#xD;
Wayne Simmonds, Nicklas Grossman, Pierre-Edouard Bellemare, Matt Read and Zac Rinaldo also score...</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2015 16:15:03 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=758005</guid></item><item><title>Task, Bruins blank Penguins 2-0; Crosby scratched late, Malkin injured</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=758004</link><description>&#xD;
PITTSBURGH, Pa. - Tuukka Rask stopped 30 shots and the Boston Bruins won their fifth game in a row, 2-0 over a Pittsburgh Penguins team missing Sidney Crosby and minus Evgeni Malkin for most of the game Saturday.&#xD;
&#xD;
Crosby, the Penguins' leading...</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2015 16:05:01 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=758004</guid></item><item><title>Sidney Crosby out of Penguins-Bruins game after skating in warmup; no reason given for scratch</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=758003</link><description>&#xD;
PITTSBURGH, Pa. - Sidney Crosby has been scratched from the lineup shortly before the Pittsburgh Penguins played the Boston Bruins.&#xD;
&#xD;
He participated in Saturday's pregame warmup but did not return for the start of the game. There was no immedi...</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2015 14:15:06 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=758003</guid></item><item><title>Around the League notebook for Friday, March 13</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757988</link><description>FRIDAY'S RESULTS&#xD;
Home Team in Caps&#xD;
Ottawa 2, NY ISLANDERS 1&#xD;
Dallas 4, WASHINGTON 2&#xD;
COLUMBUS 5, Edmonton 4 (SO)&#xD;
Anaheim 2, MINNESOTA 1&#xD;
CALGARY 6, Toronto 3&#xD;
&#xD;
ANAHEIM DEFEATS MINNESOTA, REACHES TOP OF LEAGUE STANDINGS&#xD;
&#xD;
Jakob Silfverberg (1-...</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2015 10:44:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://1.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/2015/03/hammond031315_672.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757988</guid></item><item><title>WHL Roundup: Nickles nets two, Comrie makes 36 saves as Americans down Cougars</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=758019</link><description>&#xD;
KENNEWICK, Wash. - Lucas Nickles scored twice and Eric Comrie turned aside 36 shots as the Tri-City Americans downed the Prince George Cougars 7-4 on Friday night in Western Hockey League action.&#xD;
&#xD;
Ty Comrie, Brian Williams, Maxwell James and J...</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2015 01:44:01 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=758019</guid></item><item><title>OHL Roundup: Salituro scores two on power play as 67's edge Generals</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=758016</link><description>&#xD;
OTTAWA - Dante Salituro scored both of Ottawa's goals on the power play as the 67's slipped past the Oshawa Generals 2-1 on Friday night in Ontario Hockey League action.&#xD;
&#xD;
The win also snaps a four-game losing skid for Ottawa (35-24-5).&#xD;
&#xD;
Tobi...</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 23:14:00 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=758016</guid></item><item><title>Friday's NHL Capsules</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757999</link><description>&#xD;
UNIONDALE, N.Y. - Matt Puempel and Kyle Turris scored second-period goals, and backup Andrew Hammond made 34 saves as the Ottawa Senators beat the New York Islanders 2-1 on Friday night.&#xD;
&#xD;
Ottawa improved to 9-1-1 in its last 11 games to remain...</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 22:55:03 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757999</guid></item><item><title>Sean Monahan scores twice, leads Flames to 6-3 win over Maple Leafs</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757998</link><description>&#xD;
CALGARY - Red-hot Sean Monahan scored his 26th and 27th goals in his first career three-point game as the Calgary Flames used a four-goal first period to beat the Toronto Maple Leafs 6-3 on Friday. &#xD;
&#xD;
The 20-year-old sophomore has 10 goals in h...</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 22:55:01 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757998</guid></item><item><title>QMJHL Roundup: Sullivan stops 48 shots to lead Screaming Eagles over Islanders</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=758013</link><description>&#xD;
CHARLOTTETOWN - Miguel Sullivan turned aside 48 shots as the Cape Breton Screaming Eagles got past the Charlottetown Islanders 5-3 on Friday night in Quebec Major Junior Hockey League action.&#xD;
&#xD;
Kyle Farrell scored twice, once on the power play ...</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 22:54:01 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=758013</guid></item><item><title>MacDonald stops 26 shots as Bulldogs double up Americans 4-2</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757997</link><description>&#xD;
ROCHESTER, N.Y. - Joey MacDonald made 26 saves as the Hamilton Bulldogs doubled up the host Rochester Americans 4-2 on Friday in American Hockey League action.&#xD;
&#xD;
Daniel Carr, Jake Dowell, Christian Thomas and Eric Tangradi supplied the offence ...</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 22:45:03 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757997</guid></item><item><title>Wennberg has shootout winner and 2 assists in Blue Jackets' 5-4 comeback victory over Oilers</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757996</link><description>&#xD;
COLUMBUS, Ohio - Alexander Wennberg scored the winning goal in the fifth round of the shootout to lift the Columbus Blue Jackets to a 5-4 victory over the Edmonton Oilers on Friday night.&#xD;
&#xD;
Wennberg, who scored his first NHL shootout goal on hi...</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 22:25:01 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757996</guid></item><item><title>Fiddler has goal, assist; Stars score 3 on power play to beat Capitals 4-2</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757995</link><description>&#xD;
WASHINGTON - Vernon Fiddler notched a goal and an assist, and the Dallas Stars scored three power-play goals to beat the Washington Capitals 4-2 on Friday night.&#xD;
&#xD;
Shawn Horcoff and Tyler Seguin also had man-advantage goals, and Colton Sceviour...</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 22:15:03 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757995</guid></item><item><title>Jordan Hill scores in overtime as IceCaps edge Monarchs 5-4</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757993</link><description>&#xD;
ST. JOHN'S, N.L. - Jordan Hill's first goal of the season came 1:17 into overtime as the St. John's IceCaps slipped past the visiting Manchester Monarchs 5-4 on Friday in American Hockey League action.&#xD;
&#xD;
Jason Jaffray struck twice for the IceCa...</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 21:15:03 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757993</guid></item><item><title>"Embarrassed" Maple Leaf Kadri says he's learned from three-game suspension</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757852</link><description>&#xD;
CALGARY - Nazem Kadri will be ready to move on after missing three straight games for disciplinary reasons.&#xD;
&#xD;
The Toronto Maple Leafs forward accompanied the team to Calgary on Friday, where he was to sit out his third consecutive game since mi...</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 20:05:06 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757852</guid></item><item><title>NHL suspends Blackhawks F Nordstrom for 2 games for boarding Coyotes D Ekman-Larsson</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757851</link><description>&#xD;
NEW YORK, N.Y. - The NHL has suspended Chicago Blackhawks forward Joakim Nordstrom for two games for an illegal hit on Arizona Coyotes defenceman Oliver Ekman-Larsson.&#xD;
&#xD;
The league announced the punishment Friday. Nordstrom also loses $6,631 in...</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 18:25:05 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757851</guid></item><item><title>Chicago's Nordstrom banned two games for boarding</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757927</link><description>NEW YORK – Chicago Blackhawks forward Joakim Nordstrom has been suspended for two games, without pay, for boarding Arizona Coyotes defenseman Oliver Ekman-Larsson during NHL Game No. 1011 in Glendale, Ariz., on Thursday, March 12, the National Hoc...</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 17:30:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://1.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/gallery/2015/03/469879_1426274810553.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757927</guid></item><item><title>Vancouver to host '16 CHL/NHL Top Prospects Game</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757942</link><description>The top prospects from the Canadian Hockey League eligible for the 2016 NHL Draft will get an opportunity to showcase their ability before hundreds of NHL scouts at the 2016 CHL/NHL Top Prospects Game at Pacific Coliseum in Vancouver on Jan. 28, 2...</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 16:44:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://2.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/2014/02/reinhart_021114_672.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757942</guid></item><item><title>Kadri: 'Lesson learned' from Maple Leafs discipline</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757936</link><description>CALGARY -- Nazem Kadri is ready to turn the page.&#xD;
&#xD;
The Toronto Maple Leafs forward, who will sit out his third straight game Friday for disciplinary reasons after being sent home Sunday by coach Peter Horachek for missing a team meeting, has cha...</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 15:26:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://3.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/2015/03/KADRI_031315_672.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757936</guid></item></channel></rss>