<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>NEWS IN ENGLISH</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/rss</link><description>NEWS IN ENGLISH</description><copyright>NHL Enterprises, L.P. (c) 2015 NHL. All Rights Reserved</copyright><language>en_US</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2015 22:11:40 EDT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Craig Anderson gets second straight start in goal for Ottawa Senators</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757264</link><description>&#xD;
OTTAWA - Ottawa Senators head coach Dave Cameron effectively put an end to any brewing goalie controversy Monday.&#xD;
&#xD;
Cameron announced Craig Anderson will start Tuesday when Ottawa faces Boston in a game that could have playoff implications. The...</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2015 17:05:01 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757264</guid></item><item><title>Canada-United States game to open 2016 WJC</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757352</link><description>Canada and the United States will play on the first day of the 2016 IIHF World Junior Championship. &#xD;
&#xD;
The schedule for the 2016 tournament, which will be held in Helsinki, Finland, will see the two North American teams playing Dec. 26 in a Group...</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2015 16:12:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://3.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/2015/03/2016_WJC_logo_672x412.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757352</guid></item><item><title>Invite to Canada's Olympic camp sparked improvement for Islanders' Hamonic</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757263</link><description>&#xD;
TORONTO - Travis Hamonic would've had to blow Canada's management group away with his play to make the Sochi Olympic team. Still, the New York Islanders defenceman was at orientation camp in August 2014, which meant something.&#xD;
&#xD;
"I certainly fe...</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2015 15:45:01 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757263</guid></item><item><title>Maple Leafs defenceman Polak undergoing hernia surgery, done for season</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757262</link><description>&#xD;
TORONTO - Toronto Maple Leafs defenceman Roman Polak will have season-ending hernia surgery.&#xD;
&#xD;
Polak, acquired last off-season from the St. Louis Blues, was a key shutdown player for the Leafs and had five goals and four assists in 56 games.&#xD;
&#xD;...</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2015 15:35:00 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757262</guid></item><item><title>Panthers' Luongo skates, aiming for Thursday return</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757343</link><description>Florida Panthers goaltender Roberto Luongo was on the ice Monday for the first time since he injured his shoulder during a game against the Toronto Maple Leafs on March 3, according to the Miami Herald. &#xD;
&#xD;
Luongo worked with goalie coach Robb Tal...</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2015 15:08:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://1.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/2015/03/luongo.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757343</guid></item><item><title>Maple Leafs' Polak to miss remainder of season</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757326</link><description>The Toronto Maple Leafs announced today that defenceman Roman Polak will undergo season-ending hernia surgery. Polak had registered nine points in 56 games with Toronto this season. As a result, the club has recalled defenceman Petter Granberg fro...</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2015 15:02:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://2.cdn.nhle.com/mapleleafs/images/upload/2015/01/polakpostjan13.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757326</guid></item><item><title>Hudler, Varlamov and Talbot capture NHL's three stars of the week</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757261</link><description>&#xD;
NEW YORK, - Calgary Flames centre Jiri Hudler was named the NHL's first star of the week Monday.&#xD;
&#xD;
Hudler had four goals and four assists to help Calgary earn seven of a possible eight points. He leads the Flames with 23 goals and 33 assists in...</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2015 12:15:08 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757261</guid></item><item><title>Hudler, Varlamov and Talbot named stars of week</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757229</link><description>NEW YORK – Calgary Flames center Jiri Hudler, Colorado Avalanche goaltender Semyon Varlamov and New York Rangers goaltender Cam Talbot have been named the NHL's "Three Stars" for the week ending March 8.&#xD;
&#xD;
FIRST STAR – JIRI HUDLER, C, CALGARY FLA...</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2015 12:00:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://1.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/2015/03/HudlerVarlamovTalbot_672.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757229</guid></item><item><title>Leafs' Kadri a healthy scratch versus Islanders after missing team meeting</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757260</link><description>&#xD;
TORONTO - Centre Nazem Kadri will be a healthy scratch Monday night when the Toronto Maple Leafs host the New York Islanders.&#xD;
&#xD;
The move is punishment for Kadri missing a team meeting Sunday morning.&#xD;
&#xD;
Interim coach Peter Horachek sent Kadri h...</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2015 11:45:07 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757260</guid></item><item><title>Around the League notebook for Sunday, March 8</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757221</link><description>1995 DEVILS TEAM HONORED THROUGHOUT THE WEEKEND&#xD;
&#xD;
The New Jersey Devils celebrated the 20th Anniversary of their 1995 Stanley Cup Championship. More than 20 players and coaches reunited during two days of festivities from March 7-8. The celebrati...</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 23:17:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://3.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/gallery/2015/03/498852_1425870057624.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757221</guid></item><item><title>Brassard scored in overtime, Talbot makes 29 saves in Rangers' 1-0 victory over Blackhawks</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757258</link><description>&#xD;
CHICAGO - Derick Brassard scored 32 seconds into overtime and Cam Talbot made 29 saves for his fifth shutout of the season in the New York Rangers' 1-0 victory over the Chicago Blackhawks on Sunday night.&#xD;
&#xD;
Brassard swooped in from left wing an...</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 22:25:00 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757258</guid></item><item><title>Senators give up four-goal lead in third, hold on to win 5-4 in shootout</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757257</link><description>&#xD;
OTTAWA - Erik Karlsson scored the winner in the sixth round of the shootout as the Ottawa Senators held on to defeat the Calgary Flames 5-4 on Sunday.&#xD;
&#xD;
Alex Chiasson, Milan Michalek, Mark Borowiecki and Mike Hoffman scored in regulation for th...</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 22:05:01 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757257</guid></item><item><title>OHL Roundup: Sam Bennett leads Frontenacs in 4-3 win over Knights</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757210</link><description>&#xD;
KINGSTON, Ont. - Sam Bennett scored once and set up two more and Lawson Crouse tacked on three helpers as the Kingston Frontenacs slipped past the visiting London Knights 4-3 on Sunday in Ontario Hockey League action.&#xD;
&#xD;
Spencer Watson, Ryan Ver...</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 21:54:01 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757210</guid></item><item><title>Varlamov stops 29 shots as Avalanche beat Wild 3-2 for third straight win</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757256</link><description>&#xD;
ST. PAUL, Minn. - Semyon Varlamov stopped 29 shots, Zach Redmond had a goal and an assist, and the Colorado Avalanche beat the Minnesota Wild 3-2 on Sunday night.&#xD;
&#xD;
Cody McLeod and Gabriel Landeskog also scored for Colorado, which won its third...</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 21:05:00 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757256</guid></item><item><title>Gibson makes 34 saves as Marlies keep pace in push for playoff spot</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757255</link><description>&#xD;
TORONTO - Christopher Gibson stopped 34 shots — including all 17 that came his way in the third period — as the Toronto Marlies toppled the visiting Utica Comets 3-1 on Sunday in American Hockey League play.&#xD;
&#xD;
Byron Froese opened the scoring wi...</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 20:35:01 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757255</guid></item><item><title>QMJHL Roundup: Sprong scores two as Islanders edge Titan 4-3 in OT</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757207</link><description>&#xD;
BATHURST, N.B. - Daniel Sprong opened the game with a power-play goal in the first period, then closed it out with the overtime winner as the Charlottetown Islanders edged the Acadie-Bathurst Titan 4-3 in Quebec Major Junior Hockey League action...</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 20:34:06 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757207</guid></item><item><title>NHL Capsules</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757254</link><description>&#xD;
BOSTON - Daniel Paille scored two goals, one short-handed, and Brad Marchand added a short-handed goal in the Boston Bruins' 5-3 victory over the Detroit Red Wings on Sunday.&#xD;
&#xD;
Clinging to the Eastern Conference's eighth and final playoff spot,...</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 20:15:07 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757254</guid></item><item><title>Kinkaid has 25 saves in playing for first time since being hurt 2 weeks ago, Devils win</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757253</link><description>&#xD;
NEWARK, N.J. - Adam Henrique scored two goals and Keith Kinkaid had 25 saves in his return to the lineup to lead the New Jersey Devils to a 5-2 victory over the Philadelphia Flyers on Sunday night.&#xD;
&#xD;
Jacob Josefson broke a second-period tie wit...</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 20:05:01 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757253</guid></item><item><title>Lindholm gets first career hat trick, Skinner scores 2 to rally Hurricanes past Oilers 7-4</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757132</link><description>&#xD;
RALEIGH, N.C. - Elias Lindholm had three goals and two assists, Jeff Skinner scored twice and Carolina rallied from three goals down to beat the Edmonton Oilers 7-4 on Sunday.&#xD;
&#xD;
Lindholm's hat trick was the first of his career, and Alexander Se...</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 18:15:02 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757132</guid></item><item><title>Penguins prospect Murray sets AHL shutout record</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757214</link><description>Pittsburgh Penguins goalie prospect Matthew Murray set an American Hockey League record by extending his shutout streak to 304 minutes and 11 seconds in the Wilkes-Barre/Scranton Penguins' 4-1 win against the Springfield Falcons on Sunday.&#xD;
&#xD;
Murr...</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 17:40:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://1.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/2015/03/murray_030715_672.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757214</guid></item><item><title>Paille scores 2, Marchand adds another in Bruins 5-3 win over Detroit</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757131</link><description>&#xD;
BOSTON - Daniel Paille scored two goals, one coming short-handed, and Brad Marchand added a short-handed goal to lift the Boston Bruins to a 5-3 victory over the Detroit Red Wings on Sunday.&#xD;
&#xD;
Boston, which is clinging the Eastern Conference's ...</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 15:15:06 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757131</guid></item><item><title>Maple Leafs send Kadri home, shut down Robidas</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757188</link><description>It was a busy day Sunday when the Toronto Maple Leafs convened for practice a day after a 6-1 loss to the St. Louis Blues at Air Canada Centre.&#xD;
&#xD;
Forward Nazem Kadri missed practice after being sent home by interim coach Peter Horachek for being ...</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 13:40:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://1.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/2015/03/kadri_030815_672.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757188</guid></item><item><title>Maple Leafs send Nazem Kadri home before practice for missing team meeting</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757130</link><description>&#xD;
TORONTO - Toronto Maple Leafs forward Nazem Kadri missed a team meeting and was sent home before practice, interim coach Peter Horachek said.&#xD;
&#xD;
Kadri was not on the ice for Sunday's practice, the morning after a 6-1 loss to the St. Louis Blues....</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 12:55:00 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757130</guid></item><item><title>Around the League notebook for Saturday, March 7</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757185</link><description>SATURDAY'S RESULTS&#xD;
Home Team in Caps&#xD;
Philadelphia 3, BOSTON 2 (OT)&#xD;
St. Louis 6, TORONTO 1&#xD;
TAMPA BAY 5, Dallas 4&#xD;
FLORIDA 4, NY Islanders 3 (SO)&#xD;
WASHINGTON 6, Buffalo 1&#xD;
Colorado 4, COLUMBUS 0&#xD;
Winnipeg 3, NASHVILLE 1&#xD;
Montreal 2, ARIZONA 0&#xD;
P...</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 10:40:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://1.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/2015/03/pens_030715_672.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757185</guid></item><item><title>Rogers Hometown Hockey: Thompson, Manitoba</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=756987</link><description>CITY in Canada will televise "Rogers Hometown Hockey" on Sunday at 6:30 p.m. ET, prior to the game between the Calgary Flames and Ottawa Senators. The show will also air on NHL Network in the U.S. The location this week is Thompson, Manitoba, and ...</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 03:00:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://1.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/2006/12/leach_flyers_hhof.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=756987</guid></item><item><title>WHL Roundup: Torrin White nets hat trick to lead Warriors past Blades 7-1</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757196</link><description>&#xD;
MOOSE JAW, Sask. - Torrin White scored twice in the first period and completed the hat trick just over a minute into the second as the Moose Jaw Warriors dominated the Saskatoon Blades 7-1 on Saturday night in Western Hockey League action.&#xD;
&#xD;
Br...</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 01:34:02 EST</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757196</guid></item><item><title>Saturday's NHL Capsules</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757129</link><description>&#xD;
BOSTON - Boston's Brad Marchand scored the tying goal late in regulation and added the winner in overtime as the Bruins beat the Philadelphia Flyers 3-2 on Saturday&#xD;
&#xD;
Marchand sent it to OT with 14.1 seconds left and then won it 3:52 into the e...</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 01:15:02 EST</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757129</guid></item><item><title>Vrbata scores 2, prevents 1 to help Canucks rally for 3-2 victory over Sharks</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757128</link><description>&#xD;
SAN JOSE, Calif. - Radim Vrbata scored his second goal of the game to break a tie in the third period and made an alert defensive play to preserve the lead and help the Vancouver Canucks complete the rally from a two-goal deficit to beat the San...</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 01:05:05 EST</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757128</guid></item><item><title>Blake Wheeler scores go-ahead goal, Jets win 3-1 to hand Predators 6th straight defeat</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757126</link><description>&#xD;
NASHVILLE, Tenn. - Things are going from bad to worse in Nashville.&#xD;
&#xD;
Blake Wheeler scored the go-ahead goal midway through the second period, and the Winnipeg Jets beat Nashville 3-1 on Saturday night to hand the slumping Predators their sixth...</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 00:35:00 EST</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757126</guid></item><item><title>Penguins goalie prospect earns 4th straight shutout</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757177</link><description>Pittsburgh Penguins goalie prospect Matthew Murray made 32 saves for his fourth consecutive shutout in the Wilkes-Barre/Scranton Penguins' 3-0 win against the Manchester Monarchs on Saturday.&#xD;
&#xD;
Murray, 20, has not allowed a goal in 245 minutes an...</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 00:32:00 EST</pubDate><thumbnail>http://1.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/2015/03/murray_030715_672.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757177</guid></item><item><title>No hard feelings from Leafs or Blues after Phaneuf's hit on Oshie</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757125</link><description>&#xD;
TORONTO - Dion Phaneuf's bone-jarring open-ice hit on T.J. Oshie and the response of St. Louis Blues captain David Backes left no sour feelings after the Toronto Maple Leafs' 6-1 blowout loss on Saturday.&#xD;
&#xD;
Phaneuf and Backes each got two minut...</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2015 23:25:01 EST</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757125</guid></item><item><title>Saturday's NHL Capsules</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757124</link><description>&#xD;
BOSTON - Boston's Brad Marchand scored the tying goal late in regulation and added the winner in overtime as the Bruins beat the Philadelphia Flyers 3-2 on Saturday&#xD;
&#xD;
Marchand sent it to OT with 14.1 seconds left and then won it 3:52 into the e...</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2015 23:05:25 EST</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757124</guid></item><item><title>Blake Wheeler scores go-ahead goal, Jets win 3-1 to hand Predators 6th straight defeat</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757122</link><description>&#xD;
NASHVILLE, Tenn. - Blake Wheeler scored the go-ahead goal midway through the second period, and the Winnipeg Jets beat Nashville 3-1 on Saturday night to hand the slumping Predators their sixth straight defeat.&#xD;
&#xD;
Michael Frolik and Drew Staffor...</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2015 22:55:01 EST</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757122</guid></item><item><title>OHL Roundup: Mikkel Aagaard nets hat trick as IceDogs rout 67's 8-3</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757163</link><description>&#xD;
ST. CATHARINES, Ont. - Mikkel Aagaard had a hat trick and an assist as the Niagara IceDogs won their sixth in a row by routing the Ottawa 67's 8-3 on Saturday night in Ontario Hockey League action.&#xD;
&#xD;
Carter Verhaeghe scored twice for Niagara (3...</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2015 22:54:01 EST</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757163</guid></item><item><title>Carey Price makes 29 saves to lead Canadiens past Coyotes 2-0</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757121</link><description>&#xD;
GLENDALE, Ariz. - Carey Price made 29 saves for his seventh shutout, and the Montreal Canadiens beat the slumping Arizona Coyotes 2-0 on Saturday night.&#xD;
&#xD;
Lars Eller and Brendan Gallagher scored for the Eastern Conference-leading Canadiens, who...</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2015 22:25:01 EST</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757121</guid></item><item><title>Friesen, Comets hand Bulldogs third straight loss with 3-2 victory</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757118</link><description>&#xD;
UTICA, N.Y. - Alex Friesen's goal at 7:24 of the third period stood up as the winner as the Utica Comets edged the host Hamilton Bulldogs 3-2 on Saturday in American Hockey League play.&#xD;
&#xD;
Will Acton and Cal O'Reilly also scored for the Comets (...</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2015 22:05:01 EST</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757118</guid></item><item><title>Ovechkin scores in return, Glencross gets 3 points and Capitals defeat Sabres, 6-1</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757117</link><description>&#xD;
WASHINGTON - Curtis Glencross notched a goal and two assists, Alex Ovechkin returned from a one-game absence to score his league-leading 44th goal, and the Washington Capitals defeated the Buffalo Sabres 6-1 on Saturday night.&#xD;
&#xD;
Jay Beagle adde...</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2015 21:55:50 EST</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757117</guid></item><item><title>3 early goals, Semyon Varlamov's 44 saves give Avalanche an easy 4-0 win over Blue Jackets</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757116</link><description>&#xD;
COLUMBUS, Ohio - Jarome Iginla, Gabriel Landeskog and Matt Duchene scored in the first 10 minutes, and Semyon Varlamov made 44 saves to lead the Colorado Avalanche to a 4-0 victory over Columbus Blue Jackets on Saturday night.&#xD;
&#xD;
The shutout was...</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2015 21:55:25 EST</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757116</guid></item><item><title>Killorn and Hedman score early in third period, Lightning rally to beat Stars 5-4</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757115</link><description>&#xD;
TAMPA, Fla. - Alex Killorn and Victor Hedman scored early third-period goals, and the Tampa Bay Lightning rallied to beat the Dallas Stars 5-4 on Saturday night.&#xD;
&#xD;
After Killorn scored from the low slot at 3:40, Hedman gave Tampa Bay a 4-3 lead...</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2015 21:55:01 EST</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757115</guid></item><item><title>Wedgewood, Clemmensen combine to stop 28 shots as Devils blank IceCaps</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757114</link><description>&#xD;
ST. JOHN'S, N.L. - Scott Wedgewood and Scott Clemmensen combined to make 28 saves as the Albany Devils blanked the host St. John's IceCaps 2-0 on Saturday in American Hockey League action.&#xD;
&#xD;
Wedgewood started in net for Albany and stopped 11 sh...</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2015 21:45:07 EST</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757114</guid></item></channel></rss>