<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>NEWS IN ENGLISH</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/rss</link><description>NEWS IN ENGLISH</description><copyright>NHL Enterprises, L.P. (c) 2015 NHL. All Rights Reserved</copyright><language>en_US</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2015 15:11:36 EDT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Sidney Crosby out of Penguins-Bruins game after skating in warmup; no reason given for scratch</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=758003</link><description>&#xD;
PITTSBURGH, Pa. - Sidney Crosby has been scratched from the lineup shortly before the Pittsburgh Penguins played the Boston Bruins.&#xD;
&#xD;
He participated in Saturday's pregame warmup but did not return for the start of the game. There was no immedi...</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2015 14:15:06 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=758003</guid></item><item><title>Crosby late scratch for Penguins; Malkin injured</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=758052</link><description>PITTSBURGH -- Pittsburgh Penguins centers Sidney Crosby and Evgeni Malkin are not playing against the Boston Bruins on Saturday.&#xD;
&#xD;
Crosby participated in Pittsburgh’s warm-ups and was listed in its lineup before being named a late scratch. Forwar...</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2015 13:33:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://1.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/2015/03/BRUINS_PENGUINS_031415.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=758052</guid></item><item><title>Around the League notebook for Friday, March 13</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757988</link><description>FRIDAY'S RESULTS&#xD;
Home Team in Caps&#xD;
Ottawa 2, NY ISLANDERS 1&#xD;
Dallas 4, WASHINGTON 2&#xD;
COLUMBUS 5, Edmonton 4 (SO)&#xD;
Anaheim 2, MINNESOTA 1&#xD;
CALGARY 6, Toronto 3&#xD;
&#xD;
ANAHEIM DEFEATS MINNESOTA, REACHES TOP OF LEAGUE STANDINGS&#xD;
&#xD;
Jakob Silfverberg (1-...</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2015 10:44:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://1.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/2015/03/hammond031315_672.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757988</guid></item><item><title>WHL Roundup: Nickles nets two, Comrie makes 36 saves as Americans down Cougars</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=758019</link><description>&#xD;
KENNEWICK, Wash. - Lucas Nickles scored twice and Eric Comrie turned aside 36 shots as the Tri-City Americans downed the Prince George Cougars 7-4 on Friday night in Western Hockey League action.&#xD;
&#xD;
Ty Comrie, Brian Williams, Maxwell James and J...</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2015 01:44:01 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=758019</guid></item><item><title>OHL Roundup: Salituro scores two on power play as 67's edge Generals</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=758016</link><description>&#xD;
OTTAWA - Dante Salituro scored both of Ottawa's goals on the power play as the 67's slipped past the Oshawa Generals 2-1 on Friday night in Ontario Hockey League action.&#xD;
&#xD;
The win also snaps a four-game losing skid for Ottawa (35-24-5).&#xD;
&#xD;
Tobi...</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 23:14:00 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=758016</guid></item><item><title>Friday's NHL Capsules</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757999</link><description>&#xD;
UNIONDALE, N.Y. - Matt Puempel and Kyle Turris scored second-period goals, and backup Andrew Hammond made 34 saves as the Ottawa Senators beat the New York Islanders 2-1 on Friday night.&#xD;
&#xD;
Ottawa improved to 9-1-1 in its last 11 games to remain...</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 22:55:03 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757999</guid></item><item><title>Sean Monahan scores twice, leads Flames to 6-3 win over Maple Leafs</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757998</link><description>&#xD;
CALGARY - Red-hot Sean Monahan scored his 26th and 27th goals in his first career three-point game as the Calgary Flames used a four-goal first period to beat the Toronto Maple Leafs 6-3 on Friday. &#xD;
&#xD;
The 20-year-old sophomore has 10 goals in h...</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 22:55:01 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757998</guid></item><item><title>QMJHL Roundup: Sullivan stops 48 shots to lead Screaming Eagles over Islanders</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=758013</link><description>&#xD;
CHARLOTTETOWN - Miguel Sullivan turned aside 48 shots as the Cape Breton Screaming Eagles got past the Charlottetown Islanders 5-3 on Friday night in Quebec Major Junior Hockey League action.&#xD;
&#xD;
Kyle Farrell scored twice, once on the power play ...</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 22:54:01 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=758013</guid></item><item><title>MacDonald stops 26 shots as Bulldogs double up Americans 4-2</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757997</link><description>&#xD;
ROCHESTER, N.Y. - Joey MacDonald made 26 saves as the Hamilton Bulldogs doubled up the host Rochester Americans 4-2 on Friday in American Hockey League action.&#xD;
&#xD;
Daniel Carr, Jake Dowell, Christian Thomas and Eric Tangradi supplied the offence ...</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 22:45:03 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757997</guid></item><item><title>Wennberg has shootout winner and 2 assists in Blue Jackets' 5-4 comeback victory over Oilers</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757996</link><description>&#xD;
COLUMBUS, Ohio - Alexander Wennberg scored the winning goal in the fifth round of the shootout to lift the Columbus Blue Jackets to a 5-4 victory over the Edmonton Oilers on Friday night.&#xD;
&#xD;
Wennberg, who scored his first NHL shootout goal on hi...</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 22:25:01 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757996</guid></item><item><title>Fiddler has goal, assist; Stars score 3 on power play to beat Capitals 4-2</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757995</link><description>&#xD;
WASHINGTON - Vernon Fiddler notched a goal and an assist, and the Dallas Stars scored three power-play goals to beat the Washington Capitals 4-2 on Friday night.&#xD;
&#xD;
Shawn Horcoff and Tyler Seguin also had man-advantage goals, and Colton Sceviour...</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 22:15:03 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757995</guid></item><item><title>Jordan Hill scores in overtime as IceCaps edge Monarchs 5-4</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757993</link><description>&#xD;
ST. JOHN'S, N.L. - Jordan Hill's first goal of the season came 1:17 into overtime as the St. John's IceCaps slipped past the visiting Manchester Monarchs 5-4 on Friday in American Hockey League action.&#xD;
&#xD;
Jason Jaffray struck twice for the IceCa...</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 21:15:03 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757993</guid></item><item><title>"Embarrassed" Maple Leaf Kadri says he's learned from three-game suspension</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757852</link><description>&#xD;
CALGARY - Nazem Kadri will be ready to move on after missing three straight games for disciplinary reasons.&#xD;
&#xD;
The Toronto Maple Leafs forward accompanied the team to Calgary on Friday, where he was to sit out his third consecutive game since mi...</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 20:05:06 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757852</guid></item><item><title>NHL suspends Blackhawks F Nordstrom for 2 games for boarding Coyotes D Ekman-Larsson</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757851</link><description>&#xD;
NEW YORK, N.Y. - The NHL has suspended Chicago Blackhawks forward Joakim Nordstrom for two games for an illegal hit on Arizona Coyotes defenceman Oliver Ekman-Larsson.&#xD;
&#xD;
The league announced the punishment Friday. Nordstrom also loses $6,631 in...</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 18:25:05 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757851</guid></item><item><title>Chicago's Nordstrom banned two games for boarding</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757927</link><description>NEW YORK – Chicago Blackhawks forward Joakim Nordstrom has been suspended for two games, without pay, for boarding Arizona Coyotes defenseman Oliver Ekman-Larsson during NHL Game No. 1011 in Glendale, Ariz., on Thursday, March 12, the National Hoc...</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 17:30:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://1.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/gallery/2015/03/469879_1426274810553.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757927</guid></item><item><title>Vancouver to host '16 CHL/NHL Top Prospects Game</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757942</link><description>The top prospects from the Canadian Hockey League eligible for the 2016 NHL Draft will get an opportunity to showcase their ability before hundreds of NHL scouts at the 2016 CHL/NHL Top Prospects Game at Pacific Coliseum in Vancouver on Jan. 28, 2...</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 16:44:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://2.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/2014/02/reinhart_021114_672.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757942</guid></item><item><title>Kadri: 'Lesson learned' from Maple Leafs discipline</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757936</link><description>CALGARY -- Nazem Kadri is ready to turn the page.&#xD;
&#xD;
The Toronto Maple Leafs forward, who will sit out his third straight game Friday for disciplinary reasons after being sent home Sunday by coach Peter Horachek for missing a team meeting, has cha...</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 15:26:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://3.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/2015/03/KADRI_031315_672.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757936</guid></item><item><title>Blackhawks' Nordstrom faces Player Safety hearing</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757908</link><description>Chicago Blackhawks forward Joakim Nordstrom will have a hearing Friday with the NHL Department for Player Safety for boarding Arizona Coyotes defenseman Oliver Ekman-Larsson during a game at Gila River Arena on Thursday.&#xD;
&#xD;
Ekman-Larsson was hit b...</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 14:11:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://3.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/2015/02/dddddddddddd.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757908</guid></item><item><title>Jets defenseman Ellerby recalled from AHL</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757911</link><description>The Winnipeg Jets announced they have recalled defenseman Keaton Ellerby from the St. John's IceCaps of the American Hockey League.&#xD;
&#xD;
Ellerby, 26, has played in 41 games this season with the IceCaps collecting 16 points and 32 penalty minutes. Th...</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 13:52:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://2.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/2015/03/ELLERBY_672_031315.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757911</guid></item><item><title>Bruins sign forward Vatrano to entry-level contract</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757915</link><description>Boston, MA - Boston Bruins General Manager Peter Chiarelli announced today, March 13, that the club has signed UMass-Amherst forward Frank Vatrano to an entry-level contract. Vatrano will report to the Providence Bruins.&#xD;
&#xD;
Vatrano finished up his...</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 13:20:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://3.cdn.nhle.com/bruins/images/upload/2015/03/600x400_FrankVatrano.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757915</guid></item><item><title>Otters winger Alex Debrincat making a name for himself in rookie season</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757862</link><description>&#xD;
Alex Debrincat was passed over twice in the OHL draft before joining the Erie Otters as a free agent last spring.&#xD;
&#xD;
He's made the teams who decided not to take a chance on him regret it.&#xD;
&#xD;
The five-foot-seven 160-pound American is the top-scor...</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 11:54:01 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757862</guid></item><item><title>Goalie Price drawing Hart Trophy attention as low-scoring Canadiens rise to top</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757847</link><description>&#xD;
MONTREAL - Even those reluctant to give goaltenders their vote for the Hart Trophy are having to reconsider with the season Carey Price is having for the Montreal Canadiens.&#xD;
&#xD;
Some coaches, including Washington's Barry Trotz and Florida's Gerar...</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 11:45:03 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757847</guid></item><item><title>Around the League notebook for Thursday, March 12</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757884</link><description>THURSDAY'S RESULTS&#xD;
Home Team in Caps&#xD;
BOSTON 3, Tampa Bay 2 (SO)&#xD;
PITTSBURGH 6, Edmonton 4&#xD;
Dallas 5, CAROLINA 3&#xD;
Ottawa 5, MONTREAL 2&#xD;
Columbus 3, DETROIT 1&#xD;
FLORIDA 4, Winnipeg 2&#xD;
ST. LOUIS 1, Philadelphia 0 (SO)&#xD;
COLORADO 2, New Jersey 1 (SO)&#xD;...</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 09:00:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://2.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/2015/03/topey.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757884</guid></item><item><title>Niemi makes 35 saves to shut out Predators for 2nd time this season in Sharks' 2-0 victory</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757846</link><description>&#xD;
SAN JOSE, Calif. - Antti Niemi made 35 saves to shut out Nashville for the second time this season, and Tomas Hertl scored a power-play goal late in the second period to lead the San Jose Sharks to a 2-0 victory over the Predators on Thursday ni...</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 01:25:00 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757846</guid></item><item><title>Richards, Shaw score power-play goals in Blackhawks' 2-1 win over Coyotes</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757845</link><description>&#xD;
GLENDALE, Ariz. - Brad Richards scored a tiebreaking power-play goal with 7:11 left in the third period to give the Chicago Blackhawks a 2-1 win over the Arizona Coyotes on Thursday night.&#xD;
&#xD;
Richards scored near the end of the advantage, puttin...</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 01:05:00 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757845</guid></item><item><title>Elliott earns shutout, then picks up win in shootout as Blues edge Flyers</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757844</link><description>&#xD;
ST. LOUIS - Brian Elliott didn't want to blink.&#xD;
&#xD;
The St. Louis goalie and Steve Mason, his Philadelphia counterpart, both earned shutouts on Thursday night. Elliott also came away with a win as the host Blues edged the Flyers 1-0 in a shootout...</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 00:35:08 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757844</guid></item><item><title>Thursday's NHL Capsules</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757842</link><description>&#xD;
BOSTON - Patrice Bergeron and Brad Marchand scored shootout goals to lift the Boston Bruins to a 3-2 victory over the Tampa Bay Lightning on Thursday night.&#xD;
&#xD;
Boston beat Tampa Bay for the 10th straight time, the longest active slide for a Brui...</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 00:25:01 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757842</guid></item><item><title>Semyon Varlamov back to full health, leads Avalanche to 2-1 shootout win over Devils</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757841</link><description>&#xD;
DENVER - Jarome Iginla scored in the second period and got the decisive goal in the shootout, Semyon Varlamov stopped 23 shots and the Colorado Avalanche beat the New Jersey Devils 2-1 on Thursday night.&#xD;
&#xD;
The Avs are now 1-1 on a pivotal three...</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 00:05:03 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757841</guid></item><item><title>Elliott earns shutout, then picks up win in shootout as Blues edge Flyers</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757839</link><description>&#xD;
ST. LOUIS - Columbus' Brian Elliott and Philadelphia's Steve Mason both earned shutouts, but Elliott picked up the win in a shootout as the host Blues edged the Flyers 1-0 on Thursday night.&#xD;
&#xD;
Elliott made 28 saves through overtime, and Mason s...</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 23:15:03 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757839</guid></item><item><title>Bergeron, Marchand score SO goals, Bruins edge Lightning 3-2</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757837</link><description>&#xD;
BOSTON - Patrice Bergeron and Brad Marchand scored shootout goals to lift the Boston Bruins to a 3-2 victory over the Tampa Bay Lightning on Thursday night.&#xD;
&#xD;
Boston beat Tampa Bay for the 10th straight time, the longest active slide for a Brui...</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 22:45:03 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757837</guid></item><item><title>OHL Roundup: MacInnis leads Rangers with three points in 8-1 win over Knights</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757807</link><description>&#xD;
LONDON, Ont. - Ryan MacInnis scored twice and added an assist to power the Kitchener Rangers to an 8-1 win over the London Knights in Ontario Hockey League action Thursday night.&#xD;
&#xD;
Max Iafrate also had two goals — including one shorthanded goal...</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 22:24:02 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757807</guid></item><item><title>Erik Karlsson scores twice as red-hot Senators down Canadiens 5-2</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757835</link><description>&#xD;
MONTREAL - Erik Karlsson scored twice and goalie Andrew Hammond remained unbeaten in regulation time as the Ottawa Senators downed the Montreal Canadiens 5-2 on Thursday night.&#xD;
&#xD;
Eric Condra, Mark Stone and Marc Methot also scored for Ottawa (3...</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 22:15:03 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757835</guid></item><item><title>Penguins squander huge lead, recover late for 6-4 win over sagging Edmonton</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757834</link><description>&#xD;
PITTSBURGH, Pa. - Steve Downie and Patric Hornqvist scored just over a minute apart late in the third period, and the Pittsburgh Penguins avoided an embarrassing collapse with a 6-4 win over Edmonton on Thursday night.&#xD;
&#xD;
Downie's 12th goal of t...</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 21:55:02 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757834</guid></item><item><title>Goligoski, Eakin, and Eaves have goal and assist each in Stars' 5-3 win over Hurricanes</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757833</link><description>&#xD;
RALEIGH, N.C. - Alex Goligoski, Cody Eakin and Patrick Eaves each had a goal and an assist, sparking the Dallas Stars to a 5-3 victory over the Carolina Hurricanes on Thursday night.&#xD;
&#xD;
Kari Lehtonen needed to make only 16 saves to earn the vict...</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 21:55:01 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757833</guid></item><item><title>QMJHL Roundup: Waked, Blisle lead Huskies in 5-1 win over Armada</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757798</link><description>&#xD;
BOISBRIAND, Que. - Antoine Waked had a goal and an assist while Jeremy Blisle made 21 saves as the Rouyn-Noranda Huskies downed the Blainville-Boisbriand Armada 5-1 in the lone Quebec Major Junior Hockey League game Thursday night.&#xD;
&#xD;
Jeremy Lau...</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 21:44:01 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757798</guid></item><item><title>Montreal, Winnipeg moving AHL franchises, OHL team headed to Hamilton</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757631</link><description>&#xD;
The Montreal Canadiens and Winnipeg Jets are moving their American Hockey League affiliates and the Ontario Hockey League's Belleville Bulls will play in Hamilton, Ontario, next season.&#xD;
&#xD;
Montreal is shifting its AHL team from Hamilton to St. J...</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 19:35:01 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757631</guid></item><item><title>Rangers' Klein out 3-4 weeks with upper-body injury</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757813</link><description>New York Rangers defenseman Kevin Klein will miss 3-4 weeks because of an upper-body injury, the Rangers announced Thursday.&#xD;
&#xD;
Klein, who sustained the injury blocking a shot by Alex Ovechkin on Wednesday in a 3-1 win against the Washington Capit...</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 19:05:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://1.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/gallery/2015/02/488294_1423798136211.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757813</guid></item><item><title>Anaheim Ducks send Josh Manson to minors with Vatanen, Beleskey nearing returns from injury</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757630</link><description>&#xD;
ANAHEIM, Calif. - The Anaheim Ducks have reassigned defenceman Josh Manson to the minors with Matt Beleskey and Sami Vatanen nearing return from injury.&#xD;
&#xD;
The Ducks announced the move Thursday.&#xD;
&#xD;
Manson has three assists in 28 games with Anahe...</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 18:45:01 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757630</guid></item><item><title>Sharks' Torres hopes to continue career after surgery</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757778</link><description>SAN JOSE -- San Jose Sharks forward Raffi Torres, two weeks removed from the third major right-knee surgery of his career, said he's encouraged he'll be able to return to the NHL next season.&#xD;
&#xD;
"Yeah, big-time," Torres said. "I've had a chance to...</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 18:20:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://2.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/2014/08/torres_082014_672.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757778</guid></item><item><title>OHL approves relocation and ownership transfer of Belleville Bulls to Hamilton</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757795</link><description>&#xD;
TORONTO - The Belleville Bulls will be moving to Steeltown later this year.&#xD;
&#xD;
The Ontario Hockey League's Board of Governors approved the relocation of the franchise to Hamilton starting in the 2015-'16 season, the OHL said Thursday in a releas...</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 18:14:00 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757795</guid></item></channel></rss>