<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>NEWS IN ENGLISH</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/rss</link><description>NEWS IN ENGLISH</description><copyright>NHL Enterprises, L.P. (c) 2015 NHL. All Rights Reserved</copyright><language>en_US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2015 22:11:37 EDT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Johansen's shootout goal leads Blue Jackets over Hurricanes 4-3, hold onto playoff position</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757480</link><description>&#xD;
RALEIGH, N.C. - Ryan Johansen had the only goal in the shootout, giving the Columbus Blue Jackets a 4-3 win over the Carolina Hurricanes on Tuesday night.&#xD;
&#xD;
Scott Hartnell had two goals while Rene Bourque added the other for the Blue Jackets. A...</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2015 22:05:24 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757480</guid></item><item><title>Eric Tangradi scores in overtime as Bulldogs edge Flames 2-1</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757479</link><description>&#xD;
GLEN FALLS, N.Y. - Eric Tangradi scored the winner 4:47 into overtime and Joey McDonald made 39 saves as the Hamilton Bulldogs edged the host Adirondack Flames 2-1 on Tuesday in American Hockey League action.&#xD;
&#xD;
Charles Hudon opened the scoring ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2015 22:05:01 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757479</guid></item><item><title>OHL Roundup: Crouse, Bennett lead Frontenacs to fourth straight win</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757419</link><description>&#xD;
PETERBOROUGH, Ont. - Lawson Crouse and Sam Bennett combined for seven points Tuesday night as the Kingston Frontenacs toppled the Peterborough Petes 6-2 in Ontario Hockey League action.&#xD;
&#xD;
Crouse had a pair of goals and an assist for Kingston wh...</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2015 22:04:04 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757419</guid></item><item><title>QMJHL Roundup: Cataractes pick up fourth straight win with victory over Remparts</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757418</link><description>&#xD;
SHAWINIGAN, Que. - Dylan Labbe's 15th goal of the season stood up as the eventual winner as the Shawinigan Cataractes extended their win streak to four games with a 2-1 victory over the Quebec Remparts on Tuesday night in Quebec Major Junior Hoc...</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2015 22:04:02 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757418</guid></item><item><title>Nash snaps tie in 3rd; Rangers top Islanders in final regular-season visit to Nassau Coliseum</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757478</link><description>&#xD;
UNIONDALE, N.Y. - Rick Nash scored a deflected goal to break a tie 2:50 into the third period, and the New York Rangers beat the New York Islanders in their last regular-season visit to Nassau Coliseum 2-1 on Tuesday night.&#xD;
&#xD;
After dropping the...</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2015 21:55:01 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757478</guid></item><item><title>Fiddler scores winning goal in Dallas Stars 2-1 victory over free-falling Philadelphia Flyers</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757477</link><description>&#xD;
PHILADELPHIA - Vernon Fiddler scored the go-ahead goal late in the third period to lift the Dallas Stars to a 2-1 victory over the Philadelphia Flyers on Tuesday night.&#xD;
&#xD;
Brett Ritchie also scored for the Stars, who won for just the fourth time...</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2015 21:45:03 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757477</guid></item><item><title>Lamoriello not behind Devils bench against Wild</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757515</link><description>Lou Lamoriello is not on the bench for the New Jersey Devils on Tuesday against the Minnesota Wild, instead watching the game from the press box.&#xD;
&#xD;
Lamoriello has been behind the bench as a co-coach with Adam Oates and Scott Stevens since Peter D...</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2015 20:45:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://2.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/2014/07/lou_070214_672.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757515</guid></item><item><title>Islanders top-line forward Kyle Okposo returns to lineup vs. Rangers following eye surgery</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757476</link><description>&#xD;
UNIONDALE, N.Y. - Top-line forward Kyle Okposo was back in the New York Islanders' lineup Tuesday night for a key matchup against the New York Rangers after missing 22 games following emergency surgery to fix a detached retina.&#xD;
&#xD;
Okposo returne...</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2015 19:25:00 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757476</guid></item><item><title>Blues agree to terms with defenseman Parayko</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757500</link><description>ST. LOUIS – St. Louis Blues President of Hockey Operations and General Manager Doug Armstrong announced today the club has agreed to terms on a two-year entry level contract with defenseman Colton Parayko.  &#xD;
&#xD;
Parayko has been assigned to the Blu...</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2015 18:11:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://3.cdn.nhle.com/blues/images/upload/2015/03/parayko644.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757500</guid></item><item><title>Avalanche goaltender Semyon Varlamov will sit out against Kings on Tuesday with groin ailment</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757473</link><description>&#xD;
DENVER - The Colorado Avalanche will sit goaltender Semyon Varlamov on Tuesday night against Los Angeles after he injured his groin over the weekend.&#xD;
&#xD;
Coach Patrick Roy confirmed after the morning skate that rookie Calvin Pickard will take Var...</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2015 14:05:00 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757473</guid></item><item><title>Leafs newcomers Sill, Lindstrom and Brewer were on losing end of deadline deals</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757272</link><description>&#xD;
TORONTO - Olli Jokinen felt like he took a "punch in the stomach" when he heard he'd been traded from the first-place Nashville Predators to the Toronto Maple Leafs. Jokinen could say that with some relief because he's back on a contender with t...</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2015 12:55:05 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757272</guid></item><item><title>Rangers agree to terms with Tambellini on contract</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757446</link><description>The New York Rangers agreed to terms Tuesday with forward Adam Tambellini on an entry-level contract, the team announced. Terms were not disclosed.&#xD;
&#xD;
Tambellini was selected by the Rangers in the third round (No. 65) of the 2013 NHL Draft. &#xD;
&#xD;
Ta...</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2015 12:38:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://3.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/2015/03/Tambellini_2013Draft_672x412.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757446</guid></item><item><title>Flyers sign forward Martel to entry-level contract</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757444</link><description>The Philadelphia Flyers have signed 5-8, 162-lb C Danick Martel to a three-year entry-level contract, according to general manager Ron Hextall.&#xD;
&#xD;
Martel, 20 (12/12/1994), is currently in his fourth and final season with the Blainville-Boisbriand ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2015 12:24:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://2.cdn.nhle.com/flyers/images/upload/2015/03/Martel1_20150310.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757444</guid></item><item><title>Stars sign forward Shore to entry-level contract</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757404</link><description>Dallas Stars General Manager Jim Nill announced today that the club has signed center Devin Shore to a three-year entry-level contract. Per club policy, terms of the deal were not disclosed.&#xD;
&#xD;
Shore, 20, recently completed his junior season at th...</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2015 10:41:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://2.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/2015/03/DevinShore_Maine.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757404</guid></item><item><title>Around the League notebook for Monday, March 9</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757401</link><description>MONDAY'S RESULTS&#xD;
Home Team in Caps&#xD;
NY Islanders 4, Toronto 3 (OT)&#xD;
DETROIT 5, Edmonton 2&#xD;
VANCOUVER 2, Anaheim 1&#xD;
Nashville 2, ARIZONA 1 (OT)&#xD;
SAN JOSE 2, Pittsburgh 1 (SO)&#xD;
&#xD;
PREDATORS REACH TOP OF NHL STANDINGS WITH WIN AGAINST COYOTES&#xD;
James ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2015 09:12:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://1.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/gallery/2015/03/499395_1425964821773.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757401</guid></item><item><title>Samsung Canada, NHL announce partnership</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757434</link><description>TORONTO – Samsung Canada and the National Hockey League today announced a multi-year partnership, making the global leader in innovative technology the first-ever exclusive partner in the mobile, tablet, and wearable hardware category. The partner...</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2015 09:00:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://3.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/2015/03/Samsung_NHL.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757434</guid></item><item><title>Predators snap 6-game skid, top Coyotes 2-1 in overtime on Neal's goal</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757271</link><description>&#xD;
GLENDALE, Ariz. - James Neal put in a rebound of Seth Jones' shot 2:45 into overtime to give the Nashville Predators a 2-1 victory over the Arizona Coyotes that snapped a season-worst, six-game skid on Monday night.&#xD;
&#xD;
Pekka Rinne made 27 saves ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2015 01:25:01 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757271</guid></item><item><title>Niemi makes 39 saves, stops 7 of 8 in shootout to lead Sharks past Penguins 2-1</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757270</link><description>&#xD;
SAN JOSE, Calif. - Antti Niemi made 39 saves and stopped seven of eight shootout attempts to lead the San Jose Sharks to their 10th straight home win against the Pittsburgh Penguins, 2-1 on Monday night.&#xD;
&#xD;
Tommy Wingels beat Marc-Andre Fleury w...</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2015 01:05:06 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757270</guid></item><item><title>Vancouver Canucks hold on to defeat Anaheim Ducks 2-1</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757269</link><description>&#xD;
VANCOUVER - Zack Kassian scored the winner in the third period Monday as Vancouver Canucks defeated the Anaheim Ducks 2-1.&#xD;
&#xD;
Bo Horvat had the other goal for Vancouver (38-24-4), while Eddie Lack stopped 29 shots as the Canucks beat the Ducks i...</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2015 00:45:01 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757269</guid></item><item><title>Monday's NHL Capsules</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757268</link><description>&#xD;
TORONTO - John Tavares scored 4:38 into overtime, capping the New York Islanders' two-goal comeback in a 4-3 victory over the Toronto Maple Leafs on Monday night.&#xD;
&#xD;
Tavares, an Ontario native, went around several defenders to score the winning ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2015 00:25:01 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757268</guid></item><item><title>Tavares scores overtime winner as Leafs blow lead, lose to Islanders</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757267</link><description>&#xD;
TORONTO - The effort was there for the Toronto Maple Leafs, but the result wasn't what they wanted.&#xD;
&#xD;
Two days after interim coach Peter Horachek criticized his team for a lack of effort in a blowout loss, the Leafs showed plenty but blew a thi...</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2015 22:35:01 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757267</guid></item><item><title>Sheahan nets go-ahead goal, Howard makes 36 saves in Red Wings' 5-2 win over Oilers</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757266</link><description>&#xD;
DETROIT - Riley Sheahan scored the go-ahead goal in the second period, Jimmy Howard made 36 saves, and the Detroit Red Wings snapped a two-game skid with a 5-2 victory over the Edmonton Oilers on Monday night.&#xD;
&#xD;
Niklas Kronwall, Teemu Pulkkinen...</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2015 22:25:01 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757266</guid></item><item><title>Islanders' Okposo might return Tuesday: report</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757366</link><description>New York Islanders right wing Kyle Okposo, who hasn't played since Jan. 19, could be in the lineup against the New York Rangers at Nassau Coliseum on Tuesday, according to Newsday. &#xD;
&#xD;
Okposo, who had emergency surgery to repair a detached retina,...</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2015 22:05:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://3.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/gallery/2015/01/477033_1422421861313.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757366</guid></item><item><title>Craig Anderson gets second straight start in goal for Ottawa Senators</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757264</link><description>&#xD;
OTTAWA - Ottawa Senators head coach Dave Cameron effectively put an end to any brewing goalie controversy Monday.&#xD;
&#xD;
Cameron announced Craig Anderson will start Tuesday when Ottawa faces Boston in a game that could have playoff implications. The...</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2015 17:05:01 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757264</guid></item><item><title>Canada-United States game to open 2016 WJC</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757352</link><description>Canada and the United States will play on the first day of the 2016 IIHF World Junior Championship. &#xD;
&#xD;
The schedule for the 2016 tournament, which will be held in Helsinki, Finland, will see the two North American teams playing Dec. 26 in a Group...</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2015 16:12:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://3.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/2015/03/2016_WJC_logo_672x412.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757352</guid></item><item><title>Invite to Canada's Olympic camp sparked improvement for Islanders' Hamonic</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757263</link><description>&#xD;
TORONTO - Travis Hamonic would've had to blow Canada's management group away with his play to make the Sochi Olympic team. Still, the New York Islanders defenceman was at orientation camp in August 2014, which meant something.&#xD;
&#xD;
"I certainly fe...</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2015 15:45:01 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757263</guid></item><item><title>Maple Leafs defenceman Polak undergoing hernia surgery, done for season</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757262</link><description>&#xD;
TORONTO - Toronto Maple Leafs defenceman Roman Polak will have season-ending hernia surgery.&#xD;
&#xD;
Polak, acquired last off-season from the St. Louis Blues, was a key shutdown player for the Leafs and had five goals and four assists in 56 games.&#xD;
&#xD;...</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2015 15:35:00 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757262</guid></item><item><title>Panthers' Luongo skates, aiming for Thursday return</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757343</link><description>Florida Panthers goaltender Roberto Luongo was on the ice Monday for the first time since he injured his shoulder during a game against the Toronto Maple Leafs on March 3, according to the Miami Herald. &#xD;
&#xD;
Luongo worked with goalie coach Robb Tal...</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2015 15:08:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://1.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/2015/03/luongo.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757343</guid></item><item><title>Maple Leafs' Polak to miss remainder of season</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757326</link><description>The Toronto Maple Leafs announced today that defenceman Roman Polak will undergo season-ending hernia surgery. Polak had registered nine points in 56 games with Toronto this season. As a result, the club has recalled defenceman Petter Granberg fro...</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2015 15:02:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://2.cdn.nhle.com/mapleleafs/images/upload/2015/01/polakpostjan13.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757326</guid></item><item><title>Hudler, Varlamov and Talbot capture NHL's three stars of the week</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757261</link><description>&#xD;
NEW YORK, - Calgary Flames centre Jiri Hudler was named the NHL's first star of the week Monday.&#xD;
&#xD;
Hudler had four goals and four assists to help Calgary earn seven of a possible eight points. He leads the Flames with 23 goals and 33 assists in...</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2015 12:15:08 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757261</guid></item><item><title>Hudler, Varlamov and Talbot named stars of week</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757229</link><description>NEW YORK – Calgary Flames center Jiri Hudler, Colorado Avalanche goaltender Semyon Varlamov and New York Rangers goaltender Cam Talbot have been named the NHL's "Three Stars" for the week ending March 8.&#xD;
&#xD;
FIRST STAR – JIRI HUDLER, C, CALGARY FLA...</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2015 12:00:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://1.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/2015/03/HudlerVarlamovTalbot_672.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757229</guid></item><item><title>Leafs' Kadri a healthy scratch versus Islanders after missing team meeting</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757260</link><description>&#xD;
TORONTO - Centre Nazem Kadri will be a healthy scratch Monday night when the Toronto Maple Leafs host the New York Islanders.&#xD;
&#xD;
The move is punishment for Kadri missing a team meeting Sunday morning.&#xD;
&#xD;
Interim coach Peter Horachek sent Kadri h...</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2015 11:45:07 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757260</guid></item><item><title>Around the League notebook for Sunday, March 8</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757221</link><description>1995 DEVILS TEAM HONORED THROUGHOUT THE WEEKEND&#xD;
&#xD;
The New Jersey Devils celebrated the 20th Anniversary of their 1995 Stanley Cup Championship. More than 20 players and coaches reunited during two days of festivities from March 7-8. The celebrati...</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 23:17:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://3.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/gallery/2015/03/498852_1425870057624.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757221</guid></item><item><title>Brassard scored in overtime, Talbot makes 29 saves in Rangers' 1-0 victory over Blackhawks</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757258</link><description>&#xD;
CHICAGO - Derick Brassard scored 32 seconds into overtime and Cam Talbot made 29 saves for his fifth shutout of the season in the New York Rangers' 1-0 victory over the Chicago Blackhawks on Sunday night.&#xD;
&#xD;
Brassard swooped in from left wing an...</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 22:25:00 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757258</guid></item><item><title>Senators give up four-goal lead in third, hold on to win 5-4 in shootout</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757257</link><description>&#xD;
OTTAWA - Erik Karlsson scored the winner in the sixth round of the shootout as the Ottawa Senators held on to defeat the Calgary Flames 5-4 on Sunday.&#xD;
&#xD;
Alex Chiasson, Milan Michalek, Mark Borowiecki and Mike Hoffman scored in regulation for th...</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 22:05:01 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757257</guid></item><item><title>OHL Roundup: Sam Bennett leads Frontenacs in 4-3 win over Knights</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757210</link><description>&#xD;
KINGSTON, Ont. - Sam Bennett scored once and set up two more and Lawson Crouse tacked on three helpers as the Kingston Frontenacs slipped past the visiting London Knights 4-3 on Sunday in Ontario Hockey League action.&#xD;
&#xD;
Spencer Watson, Ryan Ver...</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 21:54:01 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757210</guid></item><item><title>Varlamov stops 29 shots as Avalanche beat Wild 3-2 for third straight win</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757256</link><description>&#xD;
ST. PAUL, Minn. - Semyon Varlamov stopped 29 shots, Zach Redmond had a goal and an assist, and the Colorado Avalanche beat the Minnesota Wild 3-2 on Sunday night.&#xD;
&#xD;
Cody McLeod and Gabriel Landeskog also scored for Colorado, which won its third...</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 21:05:00 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757256</guid></item><item><title>Gibson makes 34 saves as Marlies keep pace in push for playoff spot</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757255</link><description>&#xD;
TORONTO - Christopher Gibson stopped 34 shots — including all 17 that came his way in the third period — as the Toronto Marlies toppled the visiting Utica Comets 3-1 on Sunday in American Hockey League play.&#xD;
&#xD;
Byron Froese opened the scoring wi...</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 20:35:01 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757255</guid></item><item><title>QMJHL Roundup: Sprong scores two as Islanders edge Titan 4-3 in OT</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757207</link><description>&#xD;
BATHURST, N.B. - Daniel Sprong opened the game with a power-play goal in the first period, then closed it out with the overtime winner as the Charlottetown Islanders edged the Acadie-Bathurst Titan 4-3 in Quebec Major Junior Hockey League action...</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 20:34:06 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757207</guid></item><item><title>NHL Capsules</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757254</link><description>&#xD;
BOSTON - Daniel Paille scored two goals, one short-handed, and Brad Marchand added a short-handed goal in the Boston Bruins' 5-3 victory over the Detroit Red Wings on Sunday.&#xD;
&#xD;
Clinging to the Eastern Conference's eighth and final playoff spot,...</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 20:15:07 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757254</guid></item></channel></rss>