<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>NEWS IN ENGLISH</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/rss</link><description>NEWS IN ENGLISH</description><copyright>NHL Enterprises, L.P. (c) 2015 NHL. All Rights Reserved</copyright><language>en_US</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 15:11:35 EDT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Islanders' Boychuk agrees to terms on new contract</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757744</link><description>The New York Islanders announced Thursday that defenseman Johnny Boychuk has agreed to terms on a seven-year contract.&#xD;
&#xD;
Financial details of the contract were not released, but Newsday reported the value of the contract is $42 million, for a $6 ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 15:08:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://1.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/gallery/2015/03/500160_1426186416898.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757744</guid></item><item><title>Islanders' Boychuk agrees to seven-year deal</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757743</link><description>The New York Islanders announced today that defenseman Johnny Boychuk has agreed to terms on a seven-year deal, signing through the 2021-22 season.&#xD;
&#xD;
Boychuk, 31, leads all Islanders defensemen in points (32), assists (25) and plus-minus rating (...</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 15:07:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://2.cdn.nhle.com/islanders/images/upload/2015/03/DL_3.12.15_Boychuk.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757743</guid></item><item><title>Flyers sign forward Bardreau to entry-level contract</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757745</link><description>The Philadelphia Flyers have signed forward Cole Bardreau to a three-year entry-level contract beginning with the start of the 2015-16 season, according to general manager Ron Hextall.&#xD;
 &#xD;
Bardreau, 21, recently completed a four-year career at Cor...</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 13:59:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://3.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/2015/03/BARDREAU_672_FLYERS.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757745</guid></item><item><title>Columbus Blue Jackets activate defenceman Ryan Murray after missing 5 weeks with ankle sprain</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757626</link><description>&#xD;
COLUMBUS, Ohio - The Columbus Blue Jackets have activated defenceman Ryan Murray off injured reserve after he missed five weeks with a high ankle sprain.&#xD;
&#xD;
Murray was hurt in a game against St. Louis on Feb. 6.&#xD;
&#xD;
The 21-year-old picked No. 2 o...</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 12:35:01 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757626</guid></item><item><title>Parenteau returns to Canadiens lineup after agent tweets: Therrien says timing right</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757625</link><description>&#xD;
BROSSARD, Que. - Coach Michel Therrien gave a sly smile when asked if Pierre-Alexandre Parenteau's return to the Montreal Canadiens lineup had anything to do with a tweet sent by his agent.&#xD;
&#xD;
"We saw the tweet from his agent and that made us th...</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 12:15:07 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757625</guid></item><item><title>Rangers' Klein to meet with doctor after shot block</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757721</link><description>New York Rangers defenseman Kevin Klein has returned to New York to meet with a team physician after blocking a shot Wednesday against the Washington Capitals, the Rangers announced Thursday.&#xD;
&#xD;
Klein blocked an Alex Ovechkin shot in the final min...</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 11:12:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://1.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/gallery/2015/02/488294_1423798136211.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757721</guid></item><item><title>Maple Leafs recall defenseman Brennan from AHL</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757720</link><description>The Toronto Maple Leafs announced today that defenseman TJ Brennan has been recalled from the Toronto Marlies (AHL).&#xD;
&#xD;
Brennan, 25, has skated in five regular season games with the Toronto Marlies this season, collecting one assist. Prior to bein...</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 10:59:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://3.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/2014/04/BRENNAN_041614.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757720</guid></item><item><title>Islanders' Leddy will miss  at least two weeks: report</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757707</link><description>New York Islanders defenseman Nick Leddy will be out at least two weeks because of an upper-body injury, according to Newsday.&#xD;
&#xD;
Leddy was injured during the second period of the Islanders' game Monday against the Toronto Maple Leafs, and he did ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 10:43:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://1.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/2015/03/eakin leddy.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757707</guid></item><item><title>WHL Roundup: Bjorkstrand, Henry lead Winterhawks over Silvertips</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757645</link><description>&#xD;
EVERETT, Wash. - Oliver Bjorkstrand and Adam Henry each had a pair of goals as the Portland Winterhawks downed the host Everett Silvertips 6-1 on Wednesday in Western Hockey League action.&#xD;
&#xD;
Nicolas Petan scored once and set up two more for the...</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 01:34:01 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757645</guid></item><item><title>Around the League notebook: Wednesday, March 11</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757697</link><description>WEDNESDAY'S RESULTS&#xD;
&#xD;
Home Team in CAPS&#xD;
&#xD;
TORONTO 4, Buffalo 3 (SO)&#xD;
NY Rangers 3, WASHINGTON 1&#xD;
CALGARY 6, Anaheim 3&#xD;
&#xD;
RANGERS STAY HOT, CLIMB INTO LEAGUE'S TOP SPOT&#xD;
&#xD;
J.T. Miller scored the eventual game-winning goal at 16:34 of the first pe...</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 01:30:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://3.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/2015/03/nyr buffy.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757697</guid></item><item><title>Cam Talbot helps Rangers move atop Metropolitan Division by beating Ovechkin, Capitals 3-1</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757623</link><description>&#xD;
WASHINGTON - New York Rangers goalie Cam Talbot found himself in a difficult spot, facing a 5-on-3 power play with two of the NHL's top three scorers on the ice for the Washington Capitals.&#xD;
&#xD;
With a flick of the wrist Wednesday night, Talbot ca...</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 00:25:01 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757623</guid></item><item><title>Gaudreau, Stajan each score twice as Flames double up Ducks 6-3</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757622</link><description>&#xD;
CALGARY - Johnny Gaudreau and Matt Stajan had two goals each to lead the Calgary Flames to a 6-3 win over the Anaheim Ducks on Wednesday.&#xD;
&#xD;
Sean Monahan and Jiri Hudler also scored for the Flames (37-25-5), who returned to play at the Scotiaban...</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 00:15:03 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757622</guid></item><item><title>NHL Capsules</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757621</link><description>&#xD;
WASHINGTON - Goalie Cam Talbot and the New York Rangers moved atop the Metropolitan Division by beating the Washington Capitals 3-1 Wednesday night, while overcoming Alex Ovechkin's league-leading 45th goal.&#xD;
&#xD;
Martin St. Louis, Carl Hagelin and...</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2015 23:45:03 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757621</guid></item><item><title>Cam Talbot helps Rangers move atop Metropolitan Division by beating Ovechkin, Capitals 3-1</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757620</link><description>&#xD;
WASHINGTON - Goalie Cam Talbot and the New York Rangers moved atop the Metropolitan Division by beating the Washington Capitals 3-1 Wednesday night, while overcoming Alex Ovechkin's league-leading 45th goal.&#xD;
&#xD;
Martin St. Louis, Carl Hagelin and...</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2015 22:55:00 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757620</guid></item><item><title>QMJHL Roundup: Foreurs down Voltigeurs, extend win streak to 12 games</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757640</link><description>&#xD;
DRUMMONDVILLE, Que. - Nicolas Aube-Kubel scored twice as the Val-d'Or Foreurs extended their win streak to 12 games with a 5-2 victory against the Drummondville Voltigeurs on Wednesday night in Quebec Major Junior Hockey League action.&#xD;
&#xD;
Anthon...</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2015 22:54:01 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757640</guid></item><item><title>Cousins nets hat trick, adds an assist as Phantoms toppled Marlies 4-3</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757619</link><description>&#xD;
TORONTO - Nick Cousins had three goals and an assist as the Lehigh Valley Phantoms edged the Toronto Marlies 4-3 on Wednesday night in American Hockey League action.&#xD;
&#xD;
Jason Akeson also scored for the Phantoms (27-24-7) while Andrew Gordon adde...</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2015 22:45:01 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757619</guid></item><item><title>OHL Roundup: Greyhounds' 12-game win streak halted by Battalion</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757637</link><description>&#xD;
NORTH BAY, Ont. - Nick Moutrey had two goals as the North Bay Battalion halted the Sault Ste. Marie Greyhounds' 12-game win streak with a 4-2 victory Wednesday night in Ontario Hockey League action.&#xD;
&#xD;
Alex Henriksson and Nick Paul also scored f...</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2015 21:44:06 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757637</guid></item><item><title>Backman scores a pair of goals to lead Monarchs past IceCaps 4-1</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757617</link><description>&#xD;
ST. JOHN'S, N.L. - Sean Backman had two goals and Jean-Francois Berube made 19 saves as the Manchester Monarchs downed the host St. John's IceCaps 4-1 on Wednesday night in American Hockey League play.&#xD;
&#xD;
Colin Miller had a goal and an assist fo...</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2015 21:05:01 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757617</guid></item><item><title>Roberts to work with new sports performance center</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757661</link><description>Former NHL player Gary Roberts announced plans Wednesday for a familiar role of off-ice instruction in his return to Pennsylvania. &#xD;
&#xD;
He will be the coordinator of the Sports Performance Center at the UPMC Lemieux Sports Complex in Cranberry Town...</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2015 17:00:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://1.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/2008/10/GaryRoberts_TBL_325.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757661</guid></item><item><title>Blues' Shattenkirk on track in recovery from surgery</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757674</link><description>ST. LOUIS -- Kevin Shattenkirk admitted the play was rather innocent.&#xD;
&#xD;
But on that Feb. 1 day against the Washington Capitals, once the St. Louis Blues defenseman received MRI results, the diagnosis was cut and dry.&#xD;
&#xD;
Shattenkirk, who has misse...</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2015 15:34:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://2.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/2015/02/Shattenkirk_nofade_2315.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757674</guid></item><item><title>Maple Leafs send Nazem Kadri home before practice for missing team meeting</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757614</link><description>&#xD;
TORONTO - In the latest turn in the saga of the Toronto Maple Leafs, forward Nazem Kadri was sent home from practice by an unhappy Peter Horachek for missing a team meeting.&#xD;
&#xD;
When Kadri showed up late to the team's practice facility, Horachek ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2015 12:55:01 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757614</guid></item><item><title>Panthers' Luongo won't return Thursday: report</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757588</link><description>Florida Panthers goalie Roberto Luongo will miss a third straight game Thursday against the Winnipeg Jets, according to the Miami Herald.&#xD;
&#xD;
Luongo sustained a shoulder injury March 3 against the Toronto Maple Leafs. He left the game but later ret...</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2015 12:00:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://1.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/2015/03/luongo.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757588</guid></item><item><title>Maple Leafs to hold Kadri out two more games</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757587</link><description>TORONTO -- Toronto Maple Leafs center Nazem Kadri will not play in their next two games, team president Brendan Shanahan announced Wednesday.&#xD;
&#xD;
Kadri, 24, was late for a team meeting Sunday and was made a healthy scratch for the Maple Leafs game ...</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2015 11:30:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://1.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/2015/03/kadri_030815_672.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757587</guid></item><item><title>Around the League notebook for Tuesday, March 10</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757575</link><description>TUESDAY'S RESULTS&#xD;
Home Team in Caps&#xD;
NY Rangers 2, NY ISLANDERS 1&#xD;
Dallas 2, PHILADELPHIA 1&#xD;
Columbus 4, CAROLINA 3 (SO)&#xD;
Tampa Bay 1, MONTREAL 0 (OT)&#xD;
Boston 3, OTTAWA 1&#xD;
ST. LOUIS 5, Winnipeg 4 &#xD;
MINNESOTA 6, New Jersey 2&#xD;
Los Angeles 5, COLORA...</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2015 09:00:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://1.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/gallery/2015/03/499847_1426044481120.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757575</guid></item><item><title>WHL Roundup: Nick McBride stops 55 shots as Raiders down Pats 5-3</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757558</link><description>&#xD;
PRINCE ALBERT, Sask. - Nick McBride made 55 saves as the Prince Albert Raiders extended their win streak to four games with a 5-3 victory against the visiting Regina Pats on Tuesday in Western Hockey League play.&#xD;
&#xD;
McBride turned away all 32 sh...</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2015 01:44:00 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757558</guid></item><item><title>Johansen's shootout goal leads Blue Jackets over Hurricanes 4-3, hold onto playoff position</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757489</link><description>&#xD;
RALEIGH, N.C. - Ryan Johansen was skating about as slowly as he could when he took the Blue Jackets' final attempt in a shootout with the Carolina Hurricanes.&#xD;
&#xD;
Then he found his opening.&#xD;
&#xD;
Johansen went with his forehand to sneak the puck pas...</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2015 00:25:00 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757489</guid></item><item><title>McNabb has goal, 2 assists and Quick stops 21 shots as Kings beat Avalanche 5-2</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757485</link><description>&#xD;
DENVER - Brayden McNabb had a goal and two assists, Jonathan Quick stopped 21 shots and the Los Angeles Kings beat Colorado 5-2 on Tuesday night to end the Avalanche's three-game win streak.&#xD;
&#xD;
Marian Gaborik, Jeff Carter, Kyle Clifford and Jake...</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2015 23:55:00 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757485</guid></item><item><title>Lamoriello not on Devils bench but role unchanged</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757515</link><description>ST. PAUL, Minn. -- Lou Lamoriello was not on the bench for the New Jersey Devils on Tuesday against the Minnesota Wild but said his role as co-coach has not changed.&#xD;
&#xD;
He watched the Devils' 6-2 loss from the press box; co-coaches Adam Oates and ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2015 23:25:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://2.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/2014/07/lou_070214_672.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757515</guid></item><item><title>Tuuka Rask makes 39 saves as Bruins beat Sens for third straight win</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757482</link><description>&#xD;
OTTAWA - Tuukka Rask stopped 39 shots to lead the Boston Bruins to a 3-1 win over the Ottawa Senators on Tuesday night.&#xD;
&#xD;
Ottawa native Ryan Spooner scored twice for the Bruins (34-22-10), who won their third straight. Loui Eriksson added the o...</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2015 22:35:01 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757482</guid></item><item><title>Johansen's shootout goal leads Blue Jackets over Hurricanes 4-3, hold onto playoff position</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757480</link><description>&#xD;
RALEIGH, N.C. - Ryan Johansen had the only goal in the shootout, giving the Columbus Blue Jackets a 4-3 win over the Carolina Hurricanes on Tuesday night.&#xD;
&#xD;
Scott Hartnell had two goals while Rene Bourque added the other for the Blue Jackets. A...</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2015 22:05:24 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757480</guid></item><item><title>Eric Tangradi scores in overtime as Bulldogs edge Flames 2-1</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757479</link><description>&#xD;
GLEN FALLS, N.Y. - Eric Tangradi scored the winner 4:47 into overtime and Joey McDonald made 39 saves as the Hamilton Bulldogs edged the host Adirondack Flames 2-1 on Tuesday in American Hockey League action.&#xD;
&#xD;
Charles Hudon opened the scoring ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2015 22:05:01 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757479</guid></item><item><title>OHL Roundup: Crouse, Bennett lead Frontenacs to fourth straight win</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757419</link><description>&#xD;
PETERBOROUGH, Ont. - Lawson Crouse and Sam Bennett combined for seven points Tuesday night as the Kingston Frontenacs toppled the Peterborough Petes 6-2 in Ontario Hockey League action.&#xD;
&#xD;
Crouse had a pair of goals and an assist for Kingston wh...</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2015 22:04:04 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757419</guid></item><item><title>QMJHL Roundup: Cataractes pick up fourth straight win with victory over Remparts</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757418</link><description>&#xD;
SHAWINIGAN, Que. - Dylan Labbe's 15th goal of the season stood up as the eventual winner as the Shawinigan Cataractes extended their win streak to four games with a 2-1 victory over the Quebec Remparts on Tuesday night in Quebec Major Junior Hoc...</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2015 22:04:02 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757418</guid></item><item><title>Fiddler scores winning goal in Dallas Stars 2-1 victory over free-falling Philadelphia Flyers</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757477</link><description>&#xD;
PHILADELPHIA - Vernon Fiddler scored the go-ahead goal late in the third period to lift the Dallas Stars to a 2-1 victory over the Philadelphia Flyers on Tuesday night.&#xD;
&#xD;
Brett Ritchie also scored for the Stars, who won for just the fourth time...</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2015 21:45:03 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757477</guid></item><item><title>Islanders top-line forward Kyle Okposo returns to lineup vs. Rangers following eye surgery</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757476</link><description>&#xD;
UNIONDALE, N.Y. - Top-line forward Kyle Okposo was back in the New York Islanders' lineup Tuesday night for a key matchup against the New York Rangers after missing 22 games following emergency surgery to fix a detached retina.&#xD;
&#xD;
Okposo returne...</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2015 19:25:00 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757476</guid></item><item><title>Blues agree to terms with defenseman Parayko</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757500</link><description>ST. LOUIS – St. Louis Blues President of Hockey Operations and General Manager Doug Armstrong announced today the club has agreed to terms on a two-year entry level contract with defenseman Colton Parayko.  &#xD;
&#xD;
Parayko has been assigned to the Blu...</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2015 18:11:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://3.cdn.nhle.com/blues/images/upload/2015/03/parayko644.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757500</guid></item><item><title>Avalanche goaltender Semyon Varlamov will sit out against Kings on Tuesday with groin ailment</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757473</link><description>&#xD;
DENVER - The Colorado Avalanche will sit goaltender Semyon Varlamov on Tuesday night against Los Angeles after he injured his groin over the weekend.&#xD;
&#xD;
Coach Patrick Roy confirmed after the morning skate that rookie Calvin Pickard will take Var...</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2015 14:05:00 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757473</guid></item><item><title>Leafs newcomers Sill, Lindstrom and Brewer were on losing end of deadline deals</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757272</link><description>&#xD;
TORONTO - Olli Jokinen felt like he took a "punch in the stomach" when he heard he'd been traded from the first-place Nashville Predators to the Toronto Maple Leafs. Jokinen could say that with some relief because he's back on a contender with t...</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2015 12:55:05 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757272</guid></item><item><title>Rangers agree to terms with Tambellini on contract</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757446</link><description>The New York Rangers agreed to terms Tuesday with forward Adam Tambellini on an entry-level contract, the team announced. Terms were not disclosed.&#xD;
&#xD;
Tambellini was selected by the Rangers in the third round (No. 65) of the 2013 NHL Draft. &#xD;
&#xD;
Ta...</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2015 12:38:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://3.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/2015/03/Tambellini_2013Draft_672x412.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757446</guid></item><item><title>Flyers sign forward Martel to entry-level contract</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757444</link><description>The Philadelphia Flyers have signed 5-8, 162-lb C Danick Martel to a three-year entry-level contract, according to general manager Ron Hextall.&#xD;
&#xD;
Martel, 20 (12/12/1994), is currently in his fourth and final season with the Blainville-Boisbriand ...</description><pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2015 12:24:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://2.cdn.nhle.com/flyers/images/upload/2015/03/Martel1_20150310.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757444</guid></item></channel></rss>