<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>NEWS IN ENGLISH</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/rss</link><description>NEWS IN ENGLISH</description><copyright>NHL Enterprises, L.P. (c) 2015 NHL. All Rights Reserved</copyright><language>en_US</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 18:11:37 EDT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Penguins prospect Murray sets AHL shutout record</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757214</link><description>Pittsburgh Penguins goalie prospect Matthew Murray set an American Hockey League record by extending his shutout streak to 304 minutes and 11 seconds in the Wilkes-Barre/Scranton Penguins' 4-1 win against the Springfield Falcons on Sunday.&#xD;
&#xD;
Murr...</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 17:40:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://1.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/2015/03/murray_030715_672.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757214</guid></item><item><title>Paille scores 2, Marchand adds another in Bruins 5-3 win over Detroit</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757131</link><description>&#xD;
BOSTON - Daniel Paille scored two goals, one coming short-handed, and Brad Marchand added a short-handed goal to lift the Boston Bruins to a 5-3 victory over the Detroit Red Wings on Sunday.&#xD;
&#xD;
Boston, which is clinging the Eastern Conference's ...</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 15:15:06 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757131</guid></item><item><title>Maple Leafs send Kadri home, shut down Robidas</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757188</link><description>It was a busy day Sunday when the Toronto Maple Leafs convened for practice a day after a 6-1 loss to the St. Louis Blues at Air Canada Centre.&#xD;
&#xD;
Forward Nazem Kadri missed practice after being sent home by interim coach Peter Horachek for being ...</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 13:40:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://1.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/gallery/2015/02/484649_1423027381499.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757188</guid></item><item><title>Maple Leafs send Nazem Kadri home before practice for missing team meeting</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757130</link><description>&#xD;
TORONTO - Toronto Maple Leafs forward Nazem Kadri missed a team meeting and was sent home before practice, interim coach Peter Horachek said.&#xD;
&#xD;
Kadri was not on the ice for Sunday's practice, the morning after a 6-1 loss to the St. Louis Blues....</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 12:55:00 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757130</guid></item><item><title>Around the League notebook for Saturday, March 7</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757185</link><description>SATURDAY'S RESULTS&#xD;
Home Team in Caps&#xD;
Philadelphia 3, BOSTON 2 (OT)&#xD;
St. Louis 6, TORONTO 1&#xD;
TAMPA BAY 5, Dallas 4&#xD;
FLORIDA 4, NY Islanders 3 (SO)&#xD;
WASHINGTON 6, Buffalo 1&#xD;
Colorado 4, COLUMBUS 0&#xD;
Winnipeg 3, NASHVILLE 1&#xD;
Montreal 2, ARIZONA 0&#xD;
P...</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 10:40:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://1.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/2015/03/pens_030715_672.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757185</guid></item><item><title>Rogers Hometown Hockey: Thompson, Manitoba</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=756987</link><description>CITY in Canada will televise "Rogers Hometown Hockey" on Sunday at 6:30 p.m. ET, prior to the game between the Calgary Flames and Ottawa Senators. The show will also air on NHL Network in the U.S. The location this week is Thompson, Manitoba, and ...</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 03:00:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://1.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/2006/12/leach_flyers_hhof.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=756987</guid></item><item><title>WHL Roundup: Torrin White nets hat trick to lead Warriors past Blades 7-1</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757196</link><description>&#xD;
MOOSE JAW, Sask. - Torrin White scored twice in the first period and completed the hat trick just over a minute into the second as the Moose Jaw Warriors dominated the Saskatoon Blades 7-1 on Saturday night in Western Hockey League action.&#xD;
&#xD;
Br...</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 01:34:02 EST</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757196</guid></item><item><title>Saturday's NHL Capsules</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757129</link><description>&#xD;
BOSTON - Boston's Brad Marchand scored the tying goal late in regulation and added the winner in overtime as the Bruins beat the Philadelphia Flyers 3-2 on Saturday&#xD;
&#xD;
Marchand sent it to OT with 14.1 seconds left and then won it 3:52 into the e...</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 01:15:02 EST</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757129</guid></item><item><title>Vrbata scores 2, prevents 1 to help Canucks rally for 3-2 victory over Sharks</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757128</link><description>&#xD;
SAN JOSE, Calif. - Radim Vrbata scored his second goal of the game to break a tie in the third period and made an alert defensive play to preserve the lead and help the Vancouver Canucks complete the rally from a two-goal deficit to beat the San...</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 01:05:05 EST</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757128</guid></item><item><title>Blake Wheeler scores go-ahead goal, Jets win 3-1 to hand Predators 6th straight defeat</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757126</link><description>&#xD;
NASHVILLE, Tenn. - Things are going from bad to worse in Nashville.&#xD;
&#xD;
Blake Wheeler scored the go-ahead goal midway through the second period, and the Winnipeg Jets beat Nashville 3-1 on Saturday night to hand the slumping Predators their sixth...</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 00:35:00 EST</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757126</guid></item><item><title>Penguins goalie prospect earns 4th straight shutout</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757177</link><description>Pittsburgh Penguins goalie prospect Matthew Murray made 32 saves for his fourth consecutive shutout in the Wilkes-Barre/Scranton Penguins' 3-0 win against the Manchester Monarchs on Saturday.&#xD;
&#xD;
Murray, 20, has not allowed a goal in 245 minutes an...</description><pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2015 00:32:00 EST</pubDate><thumbnail>http://1.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/2015/03/murray_030715_672.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757177</guid></item><item><title>No hard feelings from Leafs or Blues after Phaneuf's hit on Oshie</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757125</link><description>&#xD;
TORONTO - Dion Phaneuf's bone-jarring open-ice hit on T.J. Oshie and the response of St. Louis Blues captain David Backes left no sour feelings after the Toronto Maple Leafs' 6-1 blowout loss on Saturday.&#xD;
&#xD;
Phaneuf and Backes each got two minut...</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2015 23:25:01 EST</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757125</guid></item><item><title>Saturday's NHL Capsules</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757124</link><description>&#xD;
BOSTON - Boston's Brad Marchand scored the tying goal late in regulation and added the winner in overtime as the Bruins beat the Philadelphia Flyers 3-2 on Saturday&#xD;
&#xD;
Marchand sent it to OT with 14.1 seconds left and then won it 3:52 into the e...</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2015 23:05:25 EST</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757124</guid></item><item><title>Blake Wheeler scores go-ahead goal, Jets win 3-1 to hand Predators 6th straight defeat</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757122</link><description>&#xD;
NASHVILLE, Tenn. - Blake Wheeler scored the go-ahead goal midway through the second period, and the Winnipeg Jets beat Nashville 3-1 on Saturday night to hand the slumping Predators their sixth straight defeat.&#xD;
&#xD;
Michael Frolik and Drew Staffor...</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2015 22:55:01 EST</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757122</guid></item><item><title>OHL Roundup: Mikkel Aagaard nets hat trick as IceDogs rout 67's 8-3</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757163</link><description>&#xD;
ST. CATHARINES, Ont. - Mikkel Aagaard had a hat trick and an assist as the Niagara IceDogs won their sixth in a row by routing the Ottawa 67's 8-3 on Saturday night in Ontario Hockey League action.&#xD;
&#xD;
Carter Verhaeghe scored twice for Niagara (3...</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2015 22:54:01 EST</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757163</guid></item><item><title>Carey Price makes 29 saves to lead Canadiens past Coyotes 2-0</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757121</link><description>&#xD;
GLENDALE, Ariz. - Carey Price made 29 saves for his seventh shutout, and the Montreal Canadiens beat the slumping Arizona Coyotes 2-0 on Saturday night.&#xD;
&#xD;
Lars Eller and Brendan Gallagher scored for the Eastern Conference-leading Canadiens, who...</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2015 22:25:01 EST</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757121</guid></item><item><title>Friesen, Comets hand Bulldogs third straight loss with 3-2 victory</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757118</link><description>&#xD;
UTICA, N.Y. - Alex Friesen's goal at 7:24 of the third period stood up as the winner as the Utica Comets edged the host Hamilton Bulldogs 3-2 on Saturday in American Hockey League play.&#xD;
&#xD;
Will Acton and Cal O'Reilly also scored for the Comets (...</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2015 22:05:01 EST</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757118</guid></item><item><title>Ovechkin scores in return, Glencross gets 3 points and Capitals defeat Sabres, 6-1</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757117</link><description>&#xD;
WASHINGTON - Curtis Glencross notched a goal and two assists, Alex Ovechkin returned from a one-game absence to score his league-leading 44th goal, and the Washington Capitals defeated the Buffalo Sabres 6-1 on Saturday night.&#xD;
&#xD;
Jay Beagle adde...</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2015 21:55:50 EST</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757117</guid></item><item><title>3 early goals, Semyon Varlamov's 44 saves give Avalanche an easy 4-0 win over Blue Jackets</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757116</link><description>&#xD;
COLUMBUS, Ohio - Jarome Iginla, Gabriel Landeskog and Matt Duchene scored in the first 10 minutes, and Semyon Varlamov made 44 saves to lead the Colorado Avalanche to a 4-0 victory over Columbus Blue Jackets on Saturday night.&#xD;
&#xD;
The shutout was...</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2015 21:55:25 EST</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757116</guid></item><item><title>Killorn and Hedman score early in third period, Lightning rally to beat Stars 5-4</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757115</link><description>&#xD;
TAMPA, Fla. - Alex Killorn and Victor Hedman scored early third-period goals, and the Tampa Bay Lightning rallied to beat the Dallas Stars 5-4 on Saturday night.&#xD;
&#xD;
After Killorn scored from the low slot at 3:40, Hedman gave Tampa Bay a 4-3 lead...</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2015 21:55:01 EST</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757115</guid></item><item><title>Wedgewood, Clemmensen combine to stop 28 shots as Devils blank IceCaps</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757114</link><description>&#xD;
ST. JOHN'S, N.L. - Scott Wedgewood and Scott Clemmensen combined to make 28 saves as the Albany Devils blanked the host St. John's IceCaps 2-0 on Saturday in American Hockey League action.&#xD;
&#xD;
Wedgewood started in net for Albany and stopped 11 sh...</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2015 21:45:07 EST</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757114</guid></item><item><title>QMJHL Roundup: Poudrier helps Foreurs extend win streak to 11 in win over Drakkar</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757052</link><description>&#xD;
VAL-D'OR, Que. - Pierre-Maxime Poudrier scored twice and added an assist as the Val-d'Or Foreurs extended their winning streak to 11 games by beating the Baie-Comeau Drakkar 5-2 on Saturday in Quebec Major Junior Hockey League action.&#xD;
&#xD;
Anthony...</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2015 21:24:01 EST</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757052</guid></item><item><title>Marlies have five-game win streak snapped in 4-1 loss to Flames</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757113</link><description>&#xD;
TORONTO - Doug Carr stopped 29 shots — including all 19 his way in the third period — as the Adirondack Flames downed the host Toronto Marlies 4-1 on Saturday in American Hockey League action.&#xD;
&#xD;
Markus Granland and Bill Arnold had a goal and an...</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2015 20:35:01 EST</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757113</guid></item><item><title>Stars C Tyler Seguin returns to lineup after missing 10 games with knee injury</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757032</link><description>&#xD;
TAMPA, Fla. - Tyler Seguin, the Dallas Stars' second-leading scorer, is back in the lineup Saturday night after missing 10 games because of a sprained right knee.&#xD;
&#xD;
Seguin, first on the club with 29 goals and second with 59 points, returned for...</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2015 20:15:28 EST</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757032</guid></item><item><title>Ovechkin returns for Capitals against Sabres</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=756972</link><description>Washington Capitals captain Alex Ovechkin returned to the lineup against the Buffalo Sabres on Saturday.&#xD;
&#xD;
Ovechkin, who had a lower-body injury, made his decision after skating in the warm-up. &#xD;
&#xD;
"Just feel like how can I handle the puck, how c...</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2015 19:30:00 EST</pubDate><thumbnail>http://2.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/2015/03/aaaaaaa.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=756972</guid></item><item><title>After missing game, Alex Ovechkin returns to Capitals' lineup against Sabres</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757030</link><description>&#xD;
WASHINGTON - NHL goals leader Alex Ovechkin returned to the Washington Capitals' lineup Saturday night against the Buffalo Sabres.&#xD;
&#xD;
Ovechkin missed Thursday night's game against Minnesota after suffering a lower-body injury Tuesday night again...</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2015 19:25:00 EST</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757030</guid></item><item><title>Columbus Blue Jackets add left wing Rene Bourque on emergency recall from AHL Springfield</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757029</link><description>&#xD;
COLUMBUS, Ohio - The Columbus Blue Jackets have added left wing Rene Bourque on emergency recall from their American Hockey League affiliate in Springfield, Massachusetts.&#xD;
&#xD;
The 33-year-old Bourque was acquired Monday along with centre William ...</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2015 17:15:03 EST</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757029</guid></item><item><title>Bruins' Marchand scores tying goal, game-winner in 3-2 OT victory over Flyers</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757028</link><description>&#xD;
BOSTON - Boston's Brad Marchand scored the tying goal and game-winner for a 3-2 victory over the Philadelphia Flyers on Saturday&#xD;
&#xD;
Marchand sent it to OT with 14.1 seconds left in regulation and scored the winning goal with 1:08 to play in over...</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2015 16:15:03 EST</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757028</guid></item><item><title>UMass beat Notre 4-3 in 5 overtimes, longest in Division I hockey history</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757045</link><description>&#xD;
SOUTH BEND, Ind. - Shane Walsh scored the winning goal in the fifth overtime to lead UMass to a 4-3 victory over Notre Dame in the longest game in NCAA Division I ice hockey history.&#xD;
&#xD;
The first-round Hockey East tournament matchup lasted 151 m...</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2015 01:54:03 EST</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757045</guid></item><item><title>WHL Roundup: Bjorkstrand scores four as Winterhawks rout Thunderbirds</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757044</link><description>&#xD;
PORTLAND, Ore. - Despite playing 12 fewer games, Oliver Bjorkstrand is just five points away from overtaking the Western Hockey League scoring lead.&#xD;
&#xD;
Bjorkstrand scored four times on Friday night as the Portland Winterhawks routed the Seattle ...</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2015 01:54:01 EST</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757044</guid></item><item><title>Sabres prospect sets NCAA record for saves</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757055</link><description>Notre Dame freshman goaltender Calvin Petersen, a 2013 draft pick by the Buffalo Sabres, set an NCAA single-game record Friday by making 87 saves, but it wasn't enough to win the longest game in college hockey history.&#xD;
&#xD;
Shane Walsh scored 11:42 ...</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2015 01:48:00 EST</pubDate><thumbnail>http://1.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/gallery/2015/03/348454_1425711066105.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757055</guid></item><item><title>Around the League notebook for Friday, March 6</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757056</link><description>FRIDAY’S RESULTS&#xD;
Home Team in Caps&#xD;
Columbus 3, NEW JERSEY 2&#xD;
Minnesota 3, CAROLINA 1&#xD;
OTTAWA 3, Buffalo 2&#xD;
Calgary 5, DETROIT 2&#xD;
CHICAGO 2, Edmonton 1 (SO)&#xD;
Pittsburgh 5, ANAHEIM 2&#xD;
&#xD;
PENGUINS DOWN DUCKS, MALKIN MOVES INTO TIE FOR LEAGUE LEAD IN...</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2015 01:30:00 EST</pubDate><thumbnail>http://2.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/2015/03/pens030615_672.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757056</guid></item><item><title>Newcomer Vermette scores in shootout to give Blackhawks 2-1 win over Oilers</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757026</link><description>&#xD;
CHICAGO - It didn't take long for the acquistion of Antoine Vermette to pay off for the Chicago Blackhawks.&#xD;
&#xD;
Vermette, playing in his second game with Chicago, scored the lone goal of the shootout in the third round, giving the Blackhawks a 2-...</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2015 01:05:01 EST</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757026</guid></item><item><title>Penguins beat Ducks 5-2 behind with 2 goals by Hornqvist</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757025</link><description>&#xD;
ANAHEIM, Calif. - Patric Hornqvist scored twice in the second period, and the Pittsburgh Penguins also got goals from Evgeni Malkin and Blake Comeau in a 5-2 victory over the league-leading Anaheim Ducks on Friday night.&#xD;
&#xD;
Thomas Greiss made 27...</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2015 00:55:00 EST</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757025</guid></item><item><title>Friday's NHL Capsules</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757024</link><description>&#xD;
RALEIGH, N.C. - Mikael Granlund and Zach Parise scored in a two-minute span of the third period as the Minnesota Wild won their fifth game in a row, defeating the Carolina Hurricanes 3-1 Friday night.&#xD;
&#xD;
Charlie Coyle also scored for Minnesota, ...</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2015 00:25:00 EST</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757024</guid></item><item><title>Newcomer Vermette scores in shootout to give Blackhawks 2-1 win over Oilers</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757023</link><description>&#xD;
CHICAGO - Newcomer Antoine Vermette scored the lone goal of the shootout in the third round, giving the Chicago Blackhawks a 2-1 win over the Edmonton Oilers on Friday night.&#xD;
&#xD;
Vermette, acquired on Saturday from Phoenix, missed on several chan...</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2015 23:35:01 EST</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757023</guid></item><item><title>Friday's NHL Capsules</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757021</link><description>&#xD;
RALEIGH, N.C. - Mikael Granlund and Zach Parise scored in a two-minute span of the third period as the Minnesota Wild won their fifth game in a row, defeating the Carolina Hurricanes 3-1 Friday night.&#xD;
&#xD;
Charlie Coyle also scored for Minnesota, ...</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2015 23:05:00 EST</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757021</guid></item><item><title>OHL Roundup: MacInnis nets SO winner as Rangers edge Spitfires to snap skid</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757041</link><description>&#xD;
KITCHENER, Ont. - The losing streak is over for the Kitchener Rangers.&#xD;
&#xD;
Ryan MacInnis scored the winner in the shootout and also added a goal in regulation as Kitchener snapped a five-game skid with a 5-4 victory over the Windsor Spitfires on ...</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2015 23:04:03 EST</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757041</guid></item><item><title>QMJHL Roundup: Jevpalovs scores hat trick as Armada get past Remparts</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757040</link><description>&#xD;
BOISBRIAND, Que. - Nikita Jevpalovs had a hat trick to lead the Blainville-Boisbriand Armada over the Quebec Remparts 5-2 on Friday night in Quebec Major Junior Hockey League action.&#xD;
&#xD;
Alexandre Delisle-Houde and Danick Martel also scored for t...</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2015 23:04:01 EST</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757040</guid></item><item><title>Byron Froese, Petter Granberg lead AHL Marlies in 5-3 win over Flames</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757020</link><description>&#xD;
TORONTO - Byron Froese struck twice and Petter Granberg had four assists as the Toronto Marlies extended their win streak to five games by downing the Adirondack Flames 5-3 in American Hockey League action on Friday.&#xD;
&#xD;
Ryan Rupert, Connor Brown...</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2015 22:45:26 EST</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757020</guid></item></channel></rss>