<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>NEWS IN ENGLISH</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/rss</link><description>NEWS IN ENGLISH</description><copyright>NHL Enterprises, L.P. (c) 2015 NHL. All Rights Reserved</copyright><language>en_US</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 15:11:35 EDT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Blackhawks' Nordstrom faces Player Safety hearing</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757908</link><description>Chicago Blackhawks forward Joakim Nordstrom will have a hearing Friday with the NHL Department for Player Safety for boarding Arizona Coyotes defenseman Oliver Ekman-Larsson during a game at Gila River Arena on Thursday.&#xD;
&#xD;
Ekman-Larsson was hit b...</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 14:11:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://3.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/2015/02/dddddddddddd.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757908</guid></item><item><title>Jets defenseman Ellerby recalled from AHL</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757911</link><description>The Winnipeg Jets announced they have recalled defenseman Keaton Ellerby from the St. John's IceCaps of the American Hockey League.&#xD;
&#xD;
Ellerby, 26, has played in 41 games this season with the IceCaps collecting 16 points and 32 penalty minutes. Th...</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 13:52:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://2.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/2015/03/ELLERBY_672_031315.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757911</guid></item><item><title>Bruins sign forward Vatrano to entry-level contract</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757915</link><description>Boston, MA - Boston Bruins General Manager Peter Chiarelli announced today, March 13, that the club has signed UMass-Amherst forward Frank Vatrano to an entry-level contract. Vatrano will report to the Providence Bruins.&#xD;
&#xD;
Vatrano finished up his...</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 13:20:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://3.cdn.nhle.com/bruins/images/upload/2015/03/600x400_FrankVatrano.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757915</guid></item><item><title>Otters winger Alex Debrincat making a name for himself in rookie season</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757862</link><description>&#xD;
Alex Debrincat was passed over twice in the OHL draft before joining the Erie Otters as a free agent last spring.&#xD;
&#xD;
He's made the teams who decided not to take a chance on him regret it.&#xD;
&#xD;
The five-foot-seven 160-pound American is the top-scor...</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 11:54:01 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757862</guid></item><item><title>Goalie Price drawing Hart Trophy attention as low-scoring Canadiens rise to top</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757847</link><description>&#xD;
MONTREAL - Even those reluctant to give goaltenders their vote for the Hart Trophy are having to reconsider with the season Carey Price is having for the Montreal Canadiens.&#xD;
&#xD;
Some coaches, including Washington's Barry Trotz and Florida's Gerar...</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 11:45:03 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757847</guid></item><item><title>Around the League notebook for Thursday, March 12</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757884</link><description>THURSDAY'S RESULTS&#xD;
Home Team in Caps&#xD;
BOSTON 3, Tampa Bay 2 (SO)&#xD;
PITTSBURGH 6, Edmonton 4&#xD;
Dallas 5, CAROLINA 3&#xD;
Ottawa 5, MONTREAL 2&#xD;
Columbus 3, DETROIT 1&#xD;
FLORIDA 4, Winnipeg 2&#xD;
ST. LOUIS 1, Philadelphia 0 (SO)&#xD;
COLORADO 2, New Jersey 1 (SO)&#xD;...</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 09:00:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://2.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/2015/03/topey.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757884</guid></item><item><title>Niemi makes 35 saves to shut out Predators for 2nd time this season in Sharks' 2-0 victory</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757846</link><description>&#xD;
SAN JOSE, Calif. - Antti Niemi made 35 saves to shut out Nashville for the second time this season, and Tomas Hertl scored a power-play goal late in the second period to lead the San Jose Sharks to a 2-0 victory over the Predators on Thursday ni...</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 01:25:00 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757846</guid></item><item><title>Richards, Shaw score power-play goals in Blackhawks' 2-1 win over Coyotes</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757845</link><description>&#xD;
GLENDALE, Ariz. - Brad Richards scored a tiebreaking power-play goal with 7:11 left in the third period to give the Chicago Blackhawks a 2-1 win over the Arizona Coyotes on Thursday night.&#xD;
&#xD;
Richards scored near the end of the advantage, puttin...</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 01:05:00 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757845</guid></item><item><title>Elliott earns shutout, then picks up win in shootout as Blues edge Flyers</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757844</link><description>&#xD;
ST. LOUIS - Brian Elliott didn't want to blink.&#xD;
&#xD;
The St. Louis goalie and Steve Mason, his Philadelphia counterpart, both earned shutouts on Thursday night. Elliott also came away with a win as the host Blues edged the Flyers 1-0 in a shootout...</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 00:35:08 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757844</guid></item><item><title>Thursday's NHL Capsules</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757842</link><description>&#xD;
BOSTON - Patrice Bergeron and Brad Marchand scored shootout goals to lift the Boston Bruins to a 3-2 victory over the Tampa Bay Lightning on Thursday night.&#xD;
&#xD;
Boston beat Tampa Bay for the 10th straight time, the longest active slide for a Brui...</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 00:25:01 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757842</guid></item><item><title>Semyon Varlamov back to full health, leads Avalanche to 2-1 shootout win over Devils</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757841</link><description>&#xD;
DENVER - Jarome Iginla scored in the second period and got the decisive goal in the shootout, Semyon Varlamov stopped 23 shots and the Colorado Avalanche beat the New Jersey Devils 2-1 on Thursday night.&#xD;
&#xD;
The Avs are now 1-1 on a pivotal three...</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 00:05:03 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757841</guid></item><item><title>Elliott earns shutout, then picks up win in shootout as Blues edge Flyers</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757839</link><description>&#xD;
ST. LOUIS - Columbus' Brian Elliott and Philadelphia's Steve Mason both earned shutouts, but Elliott picked up the win in a shootout as the host Blues edged the Flyers 1-0 on Thursday night.&#xD;
&#xD;
Elliott made 28 saves through overtime, and Mason s...</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 23:15:03 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757839</guid></item><item><title>Bergeron, Marchand score SO goals, Bruins edge Lightning 3-2</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757837</link><description>&#xD;
BOSTON - Patrice Bergeron and Brad Marchand scored shootout goals to lift the Boston Bruins to a 3-2 victory over the Tampa Bay Lightning on Thursday night.&#xD;
&#xD;
Boston beat Tampa Bay for the 10th straight time, the longest active slide for a Brui...</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 22:45:03 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757837</guid></item><item><title>OHL Roundup: MacInnis leads Rangers with three points in 8-1 win over Knights</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757807</link><description>&#xD;
LONDON, Ont. - Ryan MacInnis scored twice and added an assist to power the Kitchener Rangers to an 8-1 win over the London Knights in Ontario Hockey League action Thursday night.&#xD;
&#xD;
Max Iafrate also had two goals — including one shorthanded goal...</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 22:24:02 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757807</guid></item><item><title>Erik Karlsson scores twice as red-hot Senators down Canadiens 5-2</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757835</link><description>&#xD;
MONTREAL - Erik Karlsson scored twice and goalie Andrew Hammond remained unbeaten in regulation time as the Ottawa Senators downed the Montreal Canadiens 5-2 on Thursday night.&#xD;
&#xD;
Eric Condra, Mark Stone and Marc Methot also scored for Ottawa (3...</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 22:15:03 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757835</guid></item><item><title>Penguins squander huge lead, recover late for 6-4 win over sagging Edmonton</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757834</link><description>&#xD;
PITTSBURGH, Pa. - Steve Downie and Patric Hornqvist scored just over a minute apart late in the third period, and the Pittsburgh Penguins avoided an embarrassing collapse with a 6-4 win over Edmonton on Thursday night.&#xD;
&#xD;
Downie's 12th goal of t...</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 21:55:02 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757834</guid></item><item><title>Goligoski, Eakin, and Eaves have goal and assist each in Stars' 5-3 win over Hurricanes</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757833</link><description>&#xD;
RALEIGH, N.C. - Alex Goligoski, Cody Eakin and Patrick Eaves each had a goal and an assist, sparking the Dallas Stars to a 5-3 victory over the Carolina Hurricanes on Thursday night.&#xD;
&#xD;
Kari Lehtonen needed to make only 16 saves to earn the vict...</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 21:55:01 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757833</guid></item><item><title>QMJHL Roundup: Waked, Blisle lead Huskies in 5-1 win over Armada</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757798</link><description>&#xD;
BOISBRIAND, Que. - Antoine Waked had a goal and an assist while Jeremy Blisle made 21 saves as the Rouyn-Noranda Huskies downed the Blainville-Boisbriand Armada 5-1 in the lone Quebec Major Junior Hockey League game Thursday night.&#xD;
&#xD;
Jeremy Lau...</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 21:44:01 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757798</guid></item><item><title>Montreal, Winnipeg moving AHL franchises, OHL team headed to Hamilton</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757631</link><description>&#xD;
The Montreal Canadiens and Winnipeg Jets are moving their American Hockey League affiliates and the Ontario Hockey League's Belleville Bulls will play in Hamilton, Ontario, next season.&#xD;
&#xD;
Montreal is shifting its AHL team from Hamilton to St. J...</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 19:35:01 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757631</guid></item><item><title>Rangers' Klein out 3-4 weeks with upper-body injury</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757813</link><description>New York Rangers defenseman Kevin Klein will miss 3-4 weeks because of an upper-body injury, the Rangers announced Thursday.&#xD;
&#xD;
Klein, who sustained the injury blocking a shot by Alex Ovechkin on Wednesday in a 3-1 win against the Washington Capit...</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 19:05:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://1.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/gallery/2015/02/488294_1423798136211.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757813</guid></item><item><title>Anaheim Ducks send Josh Manson to minors with Vatanen, Beleskey nearing returns from injury</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757630</link><description>&#xD;
ANAHEIM, Calif. - The Anaheim Ducks have reassigned defenceman Josh Manson to the minors with Matt Beleskey and Sami Vatanen nearing return from injury.&#xD;
&#xD;
The Ducks announced the move Thursday.&#xD;
&#xD;
Manson has three assists in 28 games with Anahe...</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 18:45:01 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757630</guid></item><item><title>Sharks' Torres hopes to continue career after surgery</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757778</link><description>SAN JOSE -- San Jose Sharks forward Raffi Torres, two weeks removed from the third major right-knee surgery of his career, said he's encouraged he'll be able to return to the NHL next season.&#xD;
&#xD;
"Yeah, big-time," Torres said. "I've had a chance to...</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 18:20:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://2.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/2014/08/torres_082014_672.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757778</guid></item><item><title>OHL approves relocation and ownership transfer of Belleville Bulls to Hamilton</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757795</link><description>&#xD;
TORONTO - The Belleville Bulls will be moving to Steeltown later this year.&#xD;
&#xD;
The Ontario Hockey League's Board of Governors approved the relocation of the franchise to Hamilton starting in the 2015-'16 season, the OHL said Thursday in a releas...</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 18:14:00 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757795</guid></item><item><title>Canadiens, Jets moving AHL teams next season</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757769</link><description>The American Hockey League announced Thursday that Montreal Canadiens ownership, Club de Hockey Canadien Inc., acquired and then relocated the Hamilton Bulldogs to St. John's and will begin play there in the 2015-16 season.&#xD;
&#xD;
"We are delighted in...</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 18:02:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://2.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/2014/12/Canadiens_Hudon_672_AHL.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757769</guid></item><item><title>Islanders' Boychuk agrees to terms on new contract</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757744</link><description>The New York Islanders announced Thursday that defenseman Johnny Boychuk has agreed to terms on a seven-year contract.&#xD;
&#xD;
Financial details of the contract were not released, but Newsday reported it's worth $42 million, for a $6 million annual ave...</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 15:08:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://1.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/gallery/2015/03/500160_1426186416898.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757744</guid></item><item><title>Flyers sign forward Bardreau to entry-level contract</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757745</link><description>The Philadelphia Flyers have signed forward Cole Bardreau to a three-year entry-level contract beginning with the start of the 2015-16 season, according to general manager Ron Hextall.&#xD;
 &#xD;
Bardreau, 21, recently completed a four-year career at Cor...</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 13:59:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://3.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/2015/03/BARDREAU_672_FLYERS.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757745</guid></item><item><title>Columbus Blue Jackets activate defenceman Ryan Murray after missing 5 weeks with ankle sprain</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757626</link><description>&#xD;
COLUMBUS, Ohio - The Columbus Blue Jackets have activated defenceman Ryan Murray off injured reserve after he missed five weeks with a high ankle sprain.&#xD;
&#xD;
Murray was hurt in a game against St. Louis on Feb. 6.&#xD;
&#xD;
The 21-year-old picked No. 2 o...</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 12:35:01 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757626</guid></item><item><title>Parenteau returns to Canadiens lineup after agent tweets: Therrien says timing right</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757625</link><description>&#xD;
BROSSARD, Que. - Coach Michel Therrien gave a sly smile when asked if Pierre-Alexandre Parenteau's return to the Montreal Canadiens lineup had anything to do with a tweet sent by his agent.&#xD;
&#xD;
"We saw the tweet from his agent and that made us th...</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 12:15:07 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757625</guid></item><item><title>Rangers' Klein to meet with doctor after shot block</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757721</link><description>New York Rangers defenseman Kevin Klein has returned to New York to meet with a team physician after blocking a shot Wednesday against the Washington Capitals, the Rangers announced Thursday.&#xD;
&#xD;
Klein blocked an Alex Ovechkin shot in the final min...</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 11:12:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://1.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/gallery/2015/02/488294_1423798136211.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757721</guid></item><item><title>Maple Leafs recall defenseman Brennan from AHL</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757720</link><description>The Toronto Maple Leafs announced today that defenseman TJ Brennan has been recalled from the Toronto Marlies (AHL).&#xD;
&#xD;
Brennan, 25, has skated in five regular season games with the Toronto Marlies this season, collecting one assist. Prior to bein...</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 10:59:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://3.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/2014/04/BRENNAN_041614.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757720</guid></item><item><title>Islanders' Leddy will miss  at least two weeks: report</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757707</link><description>New York Islanders defenseman Nick Leddy will be out at least two weeks because of an upper-body injury, according to Newsday.&#xD;
&#xD;
Leddy was injured during the second period of the Islanders' game Monday against the Toronto Maple Leafs, and he did ...</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 10:43:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://1.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/2015/03/eakin leddy.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757707</guid></item><item><title>WHL Roundup: Bjorkstrand, Henry lead Winterhawks over Silvertips</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757645</link><description>&#xD;
EVERETT, Wash. - Oliver Bjorkstrand and Adam Henry each had a pair of goals as the Portland Winterhawks downed the host Everett Silvertips 6-1 on Wednesday in Western Hockey League action.&#xD;
&#xD;
Nicolas Petan scored once and set up two more for the...</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 01:34:01 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757645</guid></item><item><title>Around the League notebook: Wednesday, March 11</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757697</link><description>WEDNESDAY'S RESULTS&#xD;
&#xD;
Home Team in CAPS&#xD;
&#xD;
TORONTO 4, Buffalo 3 (SO)&#xD;
NY Rangers 3, WASHINGTON 1&#xD;
CALGARY 6, Anaheim 3&#xD;
&#xD;
RANGERS STAY HOT, CLIMB INTO LEAGUE'S TOP SPOT&#xD;
&#xD;
J.T. Miller scored the eventual game-winning goal at 16:34 of the first pe...</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 01:30:00 EDT</pubDate><thumbnail>http://3.cdn.nhle.com/nhl/images/upload/2015/03/nyr buffy.jpg</thumbnail><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757697</guid></item><item><title>Cam Talbot helps Rangers move atop Metropolitan Division by beating Ovechkin, Capitals 3-1</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757623</link><description>&#xD;
WASHINGTON - New York Rangers goalie Cam Talbot found himself in a difficult spot, facing a 5-on-3 power play with two of the NHL's top three scorers on the ice for the Washington Capitals.&#xD;
&#xD;
With a flick of the wrist Wednesday night, Talbot ca...</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 00:25:01 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757623</guid></item><item><title>Gaudreau, Stajan each score twice as Flames double up Ducks 6-3</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757622</link><description>&#xD;
CALGARY - Johnny Gaudreau and Matt Stajan had two goals each to lead the Calgary Flames to a 6-3 win over the Anaheim Ducks on Wednesday.&#xD;
&#xD;
Sean Monahan and Jiri Hudler also scored for the Flames (37-25-5), who returned to play at the Scotiaban...</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 00:15:03 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757622</guid></item><item><title>NHL Capsules</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757621</link><description>&#xD;
WASHINGTON - Goalie Cam Talbot and the New York Rangers moved atop the Metropolitan Division by beating the Washington Capitals 3-1 Wednesday night, while overcoming Alex Ovechkin's league-leading 45th goal.&#xD;
&#xD;
Martin St. Louis, Carl Hagelin and...</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2015 23:45:03 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757621</guid></item><item><title>Cam Talbot helps Rangers move atop Metropolitan Division by beating Ovechkin, Capitals 3-1</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757620</link><description>&#xD;
WASHINGTON - Goalie Cam Talbot and the New York Rangers moved atop the Metropolitan Division by beating the Washington Capitals 3-1 Wednesday night, while overcoming Alex Ovechkin's league-leading 45th goal.&#xD;
&#xD;
Martin St. Louis, Carl Hagelin and...</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2015 22:55:00 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757620</guid></item><item><title>QMJHL Roundup: Foreurs down Voltigeurs, extend win streak to 12 games</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757640</link><description>&#xD;
DRUMMONDVILLE, Que. - Nicolas Aube-Kubel scored twice as the Val-d'Or Foreurs extended their win streak to 12 games with a 5-2 victory against the Drummondville Voltigeurs on Wednesday night in Quebec Major Junior Hockey League action.&#xD;
&#xD;
Anthon...</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2015 22:54:01 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757640</guid></item><item><title>Cousins nets hat trick, adds an assist as Phantoms toppled Marlies 4-3</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757619</link><description>&#xD;
TORONTO - Nick Cousins had three goals and an assist as the Lehigh Valley Phantoms edged the Toronto Marlies 4-3 on Wednesday night in American Hockey League action.&#xD;
&#xD;
Jason Akeson also scored for the Phantoms (27-24-7) while Andrew Gordon adde...</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2015 22:45:01 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757619</guid></item><item><title>OHL Roundup: Greyhounds' 12-game win streak halted by Battalion</title><link>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757637</link><description>&#xD;
NORTH BAY, Ont. - Nick Moutrey had two goals as the North Bay Battalion halted the Sault Ste. Marie Greyhounds' 12-game win streak with a 4-2 victory Wednesday night in Ontario Hockey League action.&#xD;
&#xD;
Alex Henriksson and Nick Paul also scored f...</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2015 21:44:06 EDT</pubDate><guid>http://www.nhl.com/ice/news.htm?id=757637</guid></item></channel></rss>